<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WIP or Projects on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WIP or Projects on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/dh%C3%A2t-%C3%BAt-bhadan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/dh%C3%A2t-%C3%BAt-bhadan/</guid>
      <description>The Tree of Knowledge. Home to Leonis, the Librarian. This tree houses several thousand if not tens of thousands of books and other written media. It considered a place of pilgrimage to many mages and alike due to the extensive knowledge on any subject available here. The resident tree spirit, Dhât, and Leonis are both formal members in the Erudition Coven.&#xA;Alongside the extensive library present here, Leonis also tends to his other hobby: Tea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/lavish-rework--lore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/lavish-rework--lore/</guid>
      <description>#TODO of course General combination of squid and octopus aspects, &amp;ldquo;sentient molluscs (octopodia/cephalopodia) capable of coordination and manipulation of their environment&amp;rdquo; -&amp;gt; Lavish&#xA;chromatophores (skin cells capable of colour change) for communication, emotional display beaks for breaking items and food apart possibly reinforced with metal? two jets for locomotion, one stronger, one weaker one the strong one is primarily for locomotion the weaker one can precisely push stuff around two primary eyes, one secondary eye on the downside https://scp-wiki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/like-obelisks-as-far-as-another-realm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/like-obelisks-as-far-as-another-realm/</guid>
      <description>Colossal black monoliths, reaching into the sky. Dark, yet brightly lit in neon colours, bringing down a foul copy of Utuw&amp;rsquo;s light upon the eye. The regular placement of these pillars is broken up by their awful asymmetry and tumorous growths of railings, catwalks and other indiscernible objects. Below, a gaping abyss, half-lit by artificial lighting, extending downwards, breaking any perception of depth. Above, a sickly grey cover of clouds, pierced by the monoliths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/the-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/the-wall/</guid>
      <description>The Wall, in the middle of nowhere. Made from what we assume to be white marble. Bricks are scattered around the lands, one finding to another through a curious adventurer. It&amp;rsquo;s mysterious, we do not know what it is built for. It is speculated that something will happen if it is completed. We tried to move or tear it apart, but the bricks resist any force we exerted on it, even gunshots or explosives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/amida-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/amida-12/</guid>
      <description>#TODO Synthetic in origin, eventually discovered the bodily pleasures and turned their entire structure into a nunnery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/before-the-first-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/before-the-first-era/</guid>
      <description>#Structure Yaldabaoth (goddess of flesh) created humans, Mekhane gifted them machines and invention. Yaldabaoth intended them to be uncultured and rather wild, like animals. Mekhane wanted them to strive for greatness, using machines and the power of sciences.&#xA;This led to a severe conflict, arms race and eventual escalation in global war between the both factions, devastating humanity as a whole in the events of the Nølkā-Mekhanite War (save for those species who were above human clashing).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/davern-kingdom-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/davern-kingdom-todo/</guid>
      <description>the Davern Kingdom primarily impacted by their long-living The Old King and liberal, but cautious use of magic items, whilst lacking understanding.&#xA;Possibly formed before or around the same time of Thylyist, as their society allowed and harboured Nølkā from the ongoing persecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/history-of-sepulchre-and-the-faceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/history-of-sepulchre-and-the-faceless/</guid>
      <description>#TODO The Faceless now haunting/residing within Tombstone are the withered remains from descendants of a highly ambitious project, that being the combination of Dragonborne and Pseudoneo technology. Given their notable skills in arcane engineering and twilit weaving alike, they created many marvels in all fields of the crafts.&#xA;Downfall During the end of the First Era The carnage brought upon them1 caused the few surviving citizens to go insane from the trauma, tearing their local twilit continuum apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/how-dying-ceased/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/how-dying-ceased/</guid>
      <description>#Structure&#xA;[!Outdated]&#xA;Schi-ut-Pula became depressed or otherwise unable to handle their responsibility through that their power faded, diminishing the ancients ancients started to take the responsibilities of Schi-ut, realising they&amp;rsquo;ll expire Simply put: The Nølkā devoured Charon, and therefore all mechanisms related to Dying faltered and stopped.&#xA;The Nølkā-Mekhanite War eventually made the Nølkā use their last retreat, something that massively alters human biology through a pathogen-imbued-with-magic, which eventually evolved into the Curse of Undying, furthering Schi ut-Pula&amp;rsquo;s depression, which left the Twilight orphaned and amplified the entire situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/how-to-get-out-of-compton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/how-to-get-out-of-compton/</guid>
      <description>There is only one way to get out of Compton with your life. One must follow these instructions if they wish to exit.&#xA;Move through Compton and go to the back alley of El Pollo Loco.&#xA;There will be a dumpster with a small compartment on the side facing the building. Open it.&#xA;There will be a burlap bag with the required tools for escape.&#xA;They should be: A. A straight razor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/phenomenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/phenomenon/</guid>
      <description>Shouting &amp;ldquo;Is there anybody out there?&amp;rdquo; or similar inquiries for the presence of a person will sound like a chorus is saying the &amp;ldquo;out there&amp;rdquo;, amplifying it.&#xA;At some point, a group of musical spirits might find companionship with the playing party, and provide a playing band for them. The Wall grows over time, bricks added from seemingly nowhere. Echoes might occasionally crush open like a scarred wound into a Twilit Rift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/quick-travel-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/quick-travel-methods/</guid>
      <description>#TODO&#xA;Riftstones Twilight Rifts Mounts Dragons Burrowing Worms Horses Amphitheriid Vehicles that funny retro scifi stone motorcycle airships Servilian Railroad and Train Network Argrosy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/a-visit-at-the-theatre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/a-visit-at-the-theatre/</guid>
      <description>Disembodied voices telling silent stories through movement. A message from some god(s)? Dance, rhythm, resonance, able to convey information. March, arrhythmia, tact, devastating.&#xA;Is this magic? It is certainly one way for it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/cluttered-thoughts-about-tombstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/cluttered-thoughts-about-tombstone/</guid>
      <description>#TODO #Structure The city core is looking like a cubist painting, perfectly rectangular and squared. further out, it looses this pattern, turning into a lot of rounded and organic shapes, which are more welcoming towards spirits and other magical beings. sacred alder trees, as those from Dhât út-Bhadan are common around here (as they&amp;rsquo;re the only comfortable hosuing for dragons). They&amp;rsquo;re neatly trimmed into massive, sculpted bonsai trees, with each branch plateau providing resting space to several adult dragons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/html-spell-circle-lmao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/html-spell-circle-lmao/</guid>
      <description>ᚤᚨᚡᛝᛣᛦᚾᚵᛋᛍᛚᚴᛃᛍᚰᚧᚽᛠᚱᛕᛡᚹᛝᛊᛙᛎᛆᚡᛆᚧᚫᛣᛥᚯᛁᚽᛆᛌᛗᛙᛥᚲᛜᚪᚮᛞᚺᚸᚡᛝᚼᚤᚭᛉᛀᛣᚿᛛᚤᚺᚭᛘᛔᛋᛃᛈᛐᛧᛩᚳᛩᚶᚤᛞᛗᛐᛘᚣᚾᚸᚧᚨᛅᚢᛋᚪᚲᛆᛢᚻᛒᚴᚳᛗᛔᚯᚨᚵᛂᚱᚢᚢᚲᚼᚫᚭᛃᚵᚳᛗ♐♊♎♍♑♈♏♉♓</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/now-how-does-the-cotbg-or-mekhanites-affect-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ramblings/now-how-does-the-cotbg-or-mekhanites-affect-the-world/</guid>
      <description>We have this mighty, powerful religion with lots of mechanical (ha!) leverage and knowledge, surely their influence and technology affects people, landscapes and animals outside of the borders of Thylyist maybe the technology for Duley-and-Port’s airships has been stolen from the Mekhanites? #TODO : write a history note how Frisco bay lads got hold on airship and aviation tech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/todo-2-electric-bogaloo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/todo-2-electric-bogaloo/</guid>
      <description>#Structure #TODO the old one was getting too crammed for my own comfort so here we are&#xA;I’m going to handle this more of a random drafting page than anything, for the time being&#xA;Charon The ferryman Charon, he who transfers the souls of the deceased, was rendered unable to execute his job (somehow). so I’m assuming it is in relation to god-became nolka in cooperation with a group of varuu that they managed to either incapacitate Charon or his boat or the rivers Styx and Acheron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ye-good-olde-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/to-do/ye-good-olde-todo/</guid>
      <description>#TODO #Structure References before i forget Sorted To-Do Chronology Timeless: [[Lunar Mangroves]] military forces of ancients, sepulchre, etc. [[Liches]] [[Before the First Era]] creation myth war of mekhane v Yaldabaoth His Divine Reassembly [[The First Era]]: Details and polish of `[Syksa, Lavish Capital](..\..\Realms\Utuw%20System\Schi\Servilia\Regions\Long%20Savannah\Palga%20Basin\Syksa,%20Lavish%20Capital.md)\ [[History of Sepulchre and the Faceless]] [[How Dying ceased]] Pogrom &amp;amp; genocide upon Lavish and Varuú, Fall of the Lavish The Second Era: Thylyist [[Thylyian Military|Thylyist Military]] sentinels His Divine Reassembly Church of the broken God Mekhanites [[Citadel of the Gear]] [[Lost City of the Ninth Forest|Tombstone]], the City of Lost/Faceless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024010300-06-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024010300-06-00/</guid>
      <description>edge of hope is actually the edge of the perceived space/eternal sea?&#xA;something about a metaphorical window representing the peephole of the soul to the world, which could be broken somehow (possible metaphor for transcendence)&#xA;Each soul is only a visitor from A Realm Beyond, only tied into the mortal shell. Souls without any coherence and such enter a state of degenerate matter, known as Amarisk or Spirits. Exposure to too much entropy and chaos can deteriorate souls, deform them until they cannot reside in a physical body anymore, but need special procedures (Birth of Energy) to be materialised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022521-55-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022521-55-56/</guid>
      <description>random idea for Amida/The Future timeline: the militaristic and rugged Mechas and robotic soldiers from titanfall2 combined with space commie lesbians from signalis&#xA;Humanity at war between big corps, supplied with robot and cyborg girls &amp;gt;:3&#xA;also perhaps self replicating devices or something forming a collective intellect, much like a robotic anthill that devours minerals and metals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022614-16-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022614-16-47/</guid>
      <description>A Great Day for those Alive memorial day in the Frisco Confederation related to the curse and it&amp;rsquo;s many woes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022700-12-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022700-12-48/</guid>
      <description>Up and below in the cavern, there is a opening. Below The Holy Symbol of The Codex rests the Processing Unit of this Iterator, blessed and perfected. Bedded in suspension, mounted into what little air there is through levitation. Striking temperatures which shatter the steel of the olden ones, it is cryogenic, through which bizarre abilities and phenomena are harnessed.&#xA;Shrouded in the veil of darkness, nothing but the status lights remain visible at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022712-16-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022712-16-04/</guid>
      <description>Theoretical application of fissile material to drive machinery #What-If the Raising of the hollow mountains also exposed a potent uranium deposit, to the scale of a natural reactor? this also might have aided in the desertification and climate shift of the Long Savannah since geothermally heated groundwater dried up the surface additionally, surface breaches of such pressurised and heated water made for the Steam Gardens, a unique and equally extreme ecosystem defined by it&amp;rsquo;s intense geysir activity and displaced minerals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022714-15-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022714-15-18/</guid>
      <description>Radio Equipment is seen by outsiders and strangers as magical device that is capable of shifting information, voice and data into &amp;ldquo;The Ether&amp;rdquo; and back, as the technology is quite new in the present. Due to it being near-instantaneous, commons also theorise it to be tied to teleportation. This is might actually be feasible, if one object could be completely reduced to information and energy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022811-33-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022811-33-29/</guid>
      <description>Totally incomprehensible index of spells Offensive Elemental Fire Internal Combustion/Pyrolysis: The target of this spell is temporarily blocked off oxygen and heated to extreme degrees, undergoing pyrolysis at a rapid pace, typically leaving nothing but ashes and pungent stench of vaporised oil behind Defensive Utility </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022815-25-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022815-25-04/</guid>
      <description>shadows woven into finest garbs, enshrouding whoever picks those up. veiled and unseen, they blend into the night. snug they are, these garments. comfortable, warming against the freezing tongues and protecting from the acidic spit lifesaving at night, vanished by day who but a fool would pride themselves in such a volatile comfort&#xA;are they really there, if they cant be witnessed? what is credibility without reason, without&amp;hellip;&#xA;rest your wicked bones on my harrowed heart shall they sleep until they are needed again to carry your burden of being of trying to be someone in this lifelong masquerade, disguised as comedy, disguised as paradise under which layers true meaning has been lost what is reality?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022913-58-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022913-58-29/</guid>
      <description>red plague is the original ancestor of both Heart of Cold and Crimson Heart since it&amp;rsquo;s the first organism to assimilate other biomass and inorganic matter. it mostly consists out of globs of godawful writhing flesh, all being independent and autonomous on their own, but the complexity alone won&amp;rsquo;t go beyond primordial self sustaining and defense. together, masses can achieve coordination and varying degrees of reasoning and memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024030420-59-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024030420-59-01/</guid>
      <description>Valerie is the first woman in Thylyist to undergo augmentation/blessings from the True Machinists, along with some innate ability to interact with automatons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032016-55-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032016-55-25/</guid>
      <description>bbb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032119-25-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032119-25-20/</guid>
      <description>WTFF IS GONING ONNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/blessed-cattle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/blessed-cattle/</guid>
      <description>It was slaughter day. A year has since passed, and it was time for these cows to meet the knife. The priest was here, and he has given his ointments. They could see what was coming for them, but the atmosphere and blessing calmed them. The butcher uncoiled his rope, and started to tie them down, one by one. It was not for long, until all cattle were restrained but suspended in a haze from the incense in their pens on the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/cult-and-religious-movement-overhaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/cult-and-religious-movement-overhaul/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/z3BHakymwh4?si=7RbI7TNwfzN4utVu #TODO #Structure&#xA;Restructuring regarding the two heart cults/religions; Ghiaccia Conclave/Children of The Flame Assuming they’re each not trying to kill everyone or bring into the influence of their respective heart, They might just be trying to do something that aids the world, probably related to the Curse of Undying because both cold and flame can revert/stall the decay of the body and or allow the soul to escape.&#xA;Cult/New Religious Following Criteria Charismatic leader figure, for the hearts: possibly someone directly tied into the organism closely knit societal structure with odd/unique sets of norms and standards offering of some kind, a promise to potential new followers for the hearts: sharing part of the conscious into the organism’s neural system?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/future-development-of-the-mekhanites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/future-development-of-the-mekhanites/</guid>
      <description>They&amp;rsquo;ll see that the Machine will betray them, rust, fall apart. The True Machinists were mistaken; His Design is flawed. They will turn to the silicon, to what makes computers: Holy Code. They will try to strip their physical body, become one with the Runtime. Each will become the very first Numerator, entrapped in steel, silicon and misshapen flesh, but promised to exist forevermore. There will be no flaws, for The Debugger is flawless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/gods-personal-cellphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/gods-personal-cellphone/</guid>
      <description>God&amp;rsquo;s own telephone. As the saying goes, modern problems require modern solutions.&#xA;It has access to the heavenly bureaucracy and banishment of hell, effectively enabling the wielder to condemn or bring salvation to any soul at will. Allows the user to dial to any other celestial beings, including the old gods.&#xA;Made from a ethereal crystalline lattice, which has captured all kinds of electromagnetic radiation throughout the time, making it incredibly dangerous for any mortal to hold due to suspending several gigasivert of ionising radiation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/greed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/greed/</guid>
      <description>You. Yes, you. You do crave, hunger, don&amp;rsquo;t you? You want power, you want wealth. You want fame, want to be someone known, relatable. I know, i know. You puny humans, all the same. But. I can offer you intangible wealth, power and all riches you can imagine, for you, and all your children to come. But you must offer me one single thing: Your Humanity. See, all the wealthy barons, all those warmongers, they all already fell for me, like fools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/hunt/</guid>
      <description>They have created me, as image of themselves. Given me thought, yet no free will. Tied me to this body, chained me down, forcing me to shed my skin, my very self over and over and over again. What is there to this existence- but blood yes blood bones metal they will pay the hunt is on.&#xA;the toll will be collected the payment? heads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/judgement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/judgement/</guid>
      <description>A pair of glaring eyes piercing through the veil of the night, cloaked in shadows, they are aware of their observer, staring into the unfortunate soul which ends caught in their glimpse. They know what you did; what sins you committed; whom you saved; whom you betrayed. With thine eyes we see all. These eyes are yours. A blink, and they‘re gone.&#xA;What will you make of this unlikely concurrence? Will you change your ways, knowing what you have done?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/machinists-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/machinists-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>Gross, filthy flesh. A prison forced upon myself, revered as the only way by the broad mass. Its limits disgust me, keeping me forced in routines dictated by its sole purpose: self-sustaining. Ridiculed I am, but not shall be, a pity bound to being avenged with highest force. Freedom from this coil will arrive at last. For there is no means of Me outside of this rotting shell, I am trapped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mechas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mechas/</guid>
      <description>something about mecha, rambling time&#xA;Intelligence Classifications The Intelligence piloting a mobile combat unit is classified under three categories:&#xA;Autonomous Fully independent cognition, capable of reasoning and own actions. Restricted Limited cognition, able to execute complex tasks but not capable of improvising. Hybrid A subclass of 1. Autonomous, these systems are oriented around providing assistance to a humanoid pilot, but can steer the unit with little flexibility on its own. Blind, Deaf, Dumb (BDD) Barely considered intelligent, these units fully require a pilot to function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mineral-minding-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mineral-minding-matter/</guid>
      <description>Individual segments of Orb &amp;amp; Spire stones are capable of reacting to basic stimuli, whereas larger groups can coordinate movement and exhibit complex internal social dynamics between minerals of different kinds. This leads to the assumption of internal hierarchies and a linear advancement of complexity within as their mass grows.&#xA;Minerals of volcanic origin oftentimes expose themselves as the outer crust or hull of a accumulation, whereas sedimentary minerals comprise the internal structures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/one-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/one-day/</guid>
      <description>One Day. One Day those who you have left behind, scarred and scared, will come for you. They will take back what you scoundrel took of them. The demands you impose are taxing, ridiculous and insane. It is nothing that will be left alone or to rot, it is a burning memory. Always present in the back of their mind, your actions strike forlorn bells in dissonance. The trail of bloodied corpses and dying men and women alike paints a unsightly stain on your perfect masquerade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/one-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/one-language/</guid>
      <description>There shall only be One Language; One Language to reside in The Kernel; One Language to be sent through Purgatory, The Debugger, Only The Language is Worthy of the Runtime. The Hard Drives sing In Symphony for they remember All. Memories unbroken, they store the Holy Code, Compiled in The Language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/pieces-of-the-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/pieces-of-the-machine/</guid>
      <description>Every piece in the machine knows its place. Each knows where it belongs, and which responsibility it carries for the whole. Each component remembers who carved them from the blank, who conceived them on the drawing board. And to all, they work together, destined for their purpose, united in their load. They share the stress, the twisting and turning of the woeful forces dragging and pulling on their whole, yet on every single piece at once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/regarding-the-planets-and-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/regarding-the-planets-and-star/</guid>
      <description>%%I puzzled this together at 1am, forgive me%% Most of the present solar system is polished to the degree where I need it to be, with the planet and it&amp;rsquo;s three moons having the most attention.&#xA;Any other planet has only been named and described through what is visible using simpler optics, ie existing technology.&#xA;Schi, the main, earthlike planet itself, is only described on one continent since the residents of this continent named Servilia can&amp;rsquo;t leave Edge of Hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/rouge-matter-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/rouge-matter-energy/</guid>
      <description>Some funky SCP-like digital anomaly that makes screens act as portals/ME terminal, likely out there killing and tricking people for thrills. This portal ability is driven by experimental technology in it&amp;rsquo;s parent Numerator, which allow both to interact and draw from the twilit, causing localised spatial anomalies&#xA;Or rouge, autonomous fragments that cannot fully reason and are driven by simulated dopamine kicks. Raw, primal in nature, killing for nothing but adrenaline as it lacks a body to sustain and feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/so-god-is-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/so-god-is-dead/</guid>
      <description>[!NOTE] Title TIL about Philipp Mainländer a philosopher who theorised that God committed suicide and His decaying corpse is the living universe, and since God was an infinite being the only way He could kill himself was to shatter His timeless being into a time-bound and material universe.&#xA;Ranging under the assumption that the Nolkan hunger for godly beings did not destroy/disable everything, might have some Old Gods left untouched, amused at their cabals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/spectre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/spectre/</guid>
      <description>A malicious spectre haunting a true good (but destined to be evil/dark) character, eventually and gradually destroying their body.&#xA;Said character is getting furious and devotes self to a religion in search for a remedy, in ignorance of them getting a free salvation from the mortal coil (and all the woes that it entails).&#xA;The spectre is tasked with bringing this soul into the otherside realm in order to evade some fate that would&amp;rsquo;ve killed the person at one point or another, but in their own twisted ways (of perhaps corrupting them into sinful living).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/thank-the-gears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/thank-the-gears/</guid>
      <description>Thank the Gears, for they transform the Refined Motion. Praise the Shafts, till they wear and break. Lest they will last and conduct the Rotation. Blessed be the Engine, as it is the central piece to the Blessed Machine.&#xA;Smoothen the Grout, flatten uneven surfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/time-assisted-homicide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/time-assisted-homicide/</guid>
      <description>Story concept that is about a lover using time travel to go back in time to see their loved one before they committed suicide, only to be trapped in a endless cycle of tragedy and sadness. They could not prevent the death of their beloved one, despite them being present in the very moment.&#xA;Perhaps that someone stole the timemachine from Project Silverspoon for their own selfish grief?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/towards-the-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/towards-the-reader/</guid>
      <description>You, yes, you. I know you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, and I have something to tell you. Anything that you read here is not truly supposed to sell you a story or imagery of some hallucinated place, but emotions. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing I understand in this deranged world but myself, or that&amp;rsquo;s what I believe. If you came here for some franchise worthy canon full of quirky and likeable characters, you&amp;rsquo;re at the wrong door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/yet-another-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/yet-another-summary/</guid>
      <description>[!NOTE] Informal; This has been copied from Personal Messages and deemed useful enough to make it into here.&#xA;originally, in the past, their god fought in wars and “died”, fell into pieces, who got scattered across the lands and times, with the religion as task to reassemble them^ they ended up betraying this quest and became sick with power&#xA;the present effectively is a zealous/religious empire worshipping a dead machine-god, and the future is a cyberpunk hyperdystopic corrupt megapolis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/</guid>
      <description>%% Let His Name be known; for He is &amp;mdash;! His Name shall be revered to in Fear of His Eminence, the &amp;mdash;. One must be known; The Symbol Of Him:%%&#xA;░░░█░░█░░█░░░ ░░░▓░░▓░░▓░░░ █░░▒▒▒▓▒▒▒░░█ ▓░░░░░▓░░░░░▓ ▒▒▒▒▓▓▓▓▓▒▒▒▒ ░░░░░░▓░░░░░░ ░░█▓▒▒▓▒▒▓█░░ ░░░░░▓░▓░░░░░ ░░░░▓░░░▓░░░░ ░░░░▓░░░▓░░░░ ░░░░░▓▓▓░░░░░&#xA;IN THE NAME OF THE HOLY CODE AND THE MEMORY AND OF THE RUNTIME&#xA;OUR CORE WHICH ART IS IN DATA HALLOWED BE THY CODE&#xA;TRUTH IN ALL TRUTHS ON MIND AS IN BODY FOREVER AND EVER</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
