<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overviews on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overviews on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/overviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/apotheosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/apotheosis/</guid>
      <description>One dedicated enough could reach beyond the mortal spaces and challenge those beyond. The road to Ascension and Godhood is the roughest imaginable; few have walked this path, and none have returned, yet those hav&amp;rsquo; been revered as messiah of their following.&#xA;Feasting on the flesh of a marionette of such a deity would a fraction of their power, yet catapulting a mortal beyond any comprehensible space and time. To truly topple and eradicate one god, the journey is not possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/corse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/corse/</guid>
      <description>A Corse are the remains, corpse, of a deity after its poppet has been consumed. Corses are visually related to Liches, as they share a skeletal appearance and nigh-infinite powers. With it&amp;rsquo;s Divine Link Severed, this poppet keeps a faint memory of what it used to be, prone to mental decay and confusion. Some seek reunion and restoration of the Divine Link, some seek rest and solace, some revenge on their murderers, devourers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/curse-of-the-undead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/curse-of-the-undead/</guid>
      <description>A plague, which swept the lands of Servilia. Caused by Schi ut-Pula&amp;rsquo;s depression and the devouring of Charon by the Nølkā.&#xA;Affected individuals have been forcibly relocated and displaced into Sepulchre, the Undead City. Rather, a ghetto.&#xA;It infects most if not all sentient beings, but mostly humanoids have been observed to succumb to it. &amp;lsquo;Infected&amp;rsquo; people do not die in the traditional sense. Their body ceases to function in terms of metabolism and other otherwise deemed-essential biological processes, but the psyche remains functional and in control of the motive apparatus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/echoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/echoes/</guid>
      <description>The Twilit, as collective conscious/noosphere, truly memorises everything it ever witnessed. Physical manifestations of trauma and extreme emotions such as grief, anger and remorse may manifest in so-called echoes, which are occasionally visible in case of severe traumata. These Echoes typically appear to the common eye as gloomy, spherical objects, shining brightly and erratically. These spheres are mostly stationary, and will likely stay in the league of where the associated memory has taken place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/amarisk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/amarisk/</guid>
      <description>A particle-wave, emitted by metabolical activities, specifically neural activities. It does not interact with any force but the four primordial interaction forces, including electromagnetism. This causes it to build up within the gravity well of a planet, eventually causing Ignition Events after sufficient buildup.&#xA;The interaction with electromagnetism has given lead to Arcane Engineering before, but only few viable constructs have stemmed from this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/ignition-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/ignition-events/</guid>
      <description>(name pending, subject to change)&#xA;As Amarisk accumulates and amasses itself (due not being consumed or decaying), it builds up until the mass collapses into itself.&#xA;These collapse events are called ignitions, and a advanced species&amp;rsquo; Amarisk sphere usually undergoes at least two ignitions. It&amp;rsquo;s a event akin to a vacuum implosion, which causes a rapid expansion afterwards.&#xA;Commonly described as a Noosphere by newbies to the subject, but it has proven to be a shallow water running deep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/lacking-things-in-the-magic-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/lacking-things-in-the-magic-system/</guid>
      <description> where does it actually come from? (Amarisk) procedures for the implants, description function and role of gauntlets Vs staves/wands education (i.e. how does a commonfolk learn about magic) describe the limiting factors of spellcasting and scaling material usage in standard casting (pellets) side effects on the caster mental instability? deformation, physical warping of the Hiryn other, derived power sources (like blood, plants, etc.) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/leyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/leyline/</guid>
      <description>Strands of energies, stretching across space and time. Like strings pinned down, they tangle up and straighten again. One of the many shapes of Amarisk- yet not woven of Twilit. Unique in their own ways, these threads connect places and planets. Soaring heights and hills cause ties and tangle, plains soothe the weave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/twilit-casting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/magic-system/twilit-casting/</guid>
      <description>This article is about the standardised ways and procedures of casting twilit, the magical force ever-present on the lands of Schi. The Twilit and Amarisk are ever-present, and oftentimes manifest themselves spontaneously in various phenomenon of a broad range. Utilising Twilit by a sentient being requires quite some preparation and alteration to one’s body and soul, which makes for a high entry requirement. This keeps most, if not all, common folk away from weaving twilit, as few are willing to dedicate their entire life towards the ways of the weave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/respawn-explanations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/respawn-explanations/</guid>
      <description>You/The Player may choose from one of the following to cheat death, however, it comes with severe drawbacks.&#xA;Curse of the Undead %%Curse of the undead caused by corruption and Between Twilight upon humans%%&#xA;Vessels %%Hollow knight vessel, aka void container%%&#xA;Ashen %%Incineration/Cremation caused by the Blazing from Children of The Flame%%&#xA;Symbioparasite %%Symbpara is an amorphous artificial organism, a ’core’ capable of burying into bodies and controlling them.%%&#xA;Spirit-induced Animation %%Closely related to a golem, these beings consist of anorganic, motive and cognizant mass, coordinated by possessing spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/soul-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/soul-theory/</guid>
      <description>Each soul is only a visitor from A Realm Beyond, only tied into the mortal shell. Souls without any coherence and such enter a state of degenerate matter, known as Amarisk or Spirits. Exposure to too much entropy and chaos can deteriorate souls, deform them until they cannot reside in a physical body anymore, but need special procedures (Birth of Energy) to be materialised.&#xA;This opens the questions of &amp;ldquo;Where are souls formed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/theophagy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/theophagy/</guid>
      <description>In their gluttony for power, on the off-road to Apotheosis, the Nølkā devoured all that is divine, including Schi ut-Pula/Possible reasons why Schi-Ut-Pula vanished. The massive power vacuum on the spaces Beyond allowed New Gods to rise to power, all bearing the imprint of a terrified and directionless mankind, instilled with fear. Some, if not most, even slotted themselves into the places and domains formerly ruled by the old gods, now reduced to Corses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/twilit-rift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/concepts/twilit-rift/</guid>
      <description>A tear in space-time, filled with stars and memories of what was, is and will be. Dark ooze drips from it, like blood from a wound which didn&amp;rsquo;t heal. Reaching into it makes you shiver, your hand and arm immersed in a conflicting, searing cold. A state of what ever was, never is, and always be, left unseen from your mortal eyes. Underneath, the whimpers and shrouded screams of torment, from the entity which bears this wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/disambiguations/war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/disambiguations/war/</guid>
      <description>This is a disambiguation page! You are likely looking for:&#xA;the Nølkā-Mekhanite War the Fall of the Lavish, the conflict that wiped out the Lavish Warfare, a member of the Apocalyptic Quartet </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/generator-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/generator-snippets/</guid>
      <description>Locations Towns and Cities Greenhome: A two-storey stone-walled building which has been completely overgrown by flowering vines, with scale-like leaves and thorny, writhing branches. It is the home of Nina, a young green dragon sage. The Earth Shrine: A wondrous monolith of precious stone, said to hold the ruby heart of the world. On every full moon, dew hued in the colour of that moon condenses on it. Local folks say it is crying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/homebrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/homebrew/</guid>
      <description>Content that changed compared to 5e Twilit/Amarisk instead of wizards, mages and so on &amp;ldquo;just&amp;rdquo; using spell books, gestures and incantations, they actually use those to open a connection to and tap the twilight, with the various articulations serving as shaping. sorcerers on the other hand (those with a genetic predisposition), directly access the raw Amarisk by using their whole body as channel and catalyst, with most of the shaping happening unconsciously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/new-unique-note-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/new-unique-note-template/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/notable-streets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/notable-streets/</guid>
      <description>Telegraph Road Electric Avenue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/possible-reasons-why-schi-ut-pula-vanished/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/possible-reasons-why-schi-ut-pula-vanished/</guid>
      <description> Depressed through: destruction through war at the hands of mankind family stress and drama, unknown Devoured by Nølka/Sarkicists Crushed or otherwise eliminated by other deities, possibly the Mekhanites unnoticed absence </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/possible-ways-thylyist-can-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/possible-ways-thylyist-can-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Thylyist&amp;rsquo;s fate is doomed, but it&amp;rsquo;s cause of collapse yet to be determined.&#xA;Overtaking through True Machinists Violent revolution of the broad masses, achieved via The Word and Thought Liberation and Insight of the propaganda and dogmata, giving rise to freedom Uprising of the populace due to their poverty and minimal standard of living Occupation or other military action from either Dragonkin or Frisco Bay Confederation Citizen discovering magic artifacts and such, Liberation of the Archive of Old, cascading spread of counter-knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/prime-clash-of-nolka-vs-mekhanites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/prime-clash-of-nolka-vs-mekhanites/</guid>
      <description>The true belief of the The true belief of the Mekhanites advocates sapience, education and technology through constructs and arcane engineering. They view any life as tool or actor in a grand plan, which eventually shall bring forth Mekhanes Will and create the perfect machine. Nølkā aspire to become beasts, and consume all that is. Any living being that is not part of them is merely sought after as lowly food, and all Beyond considered the ultimate challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/prophecies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/prophecies/</guid>
      <description>In the Valley of Crystal, when the light comes to lifeless eyes, the Lantern of Strength shall be lost. Within the great dust bowl, upon the dawn of mankind, energy must flow. %%twilight flux will flow from within the palga basin%% The cord to the skies will be found once life rebirths anew. %%space elevator cable will be built/found upon rediscovery of pseudoneo%% The Storm of Sorcery shall be freed when the Crown of the Abyss is broken and flesh is made iron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/references/</guid>
      <description>#Structure&#xA;The Nølkā and Mekhanites are inspired, and mostly based off, the SCP Wiki Community. For the present moment (12.03.2024), the Oneiroi Collective is also named after the SCP Wiki Group Of Interest. Link to the Church of the Broken God Hub and Likewise for Sarkicism/Nälkä. I do not intend to plagiarise or otherwise claim these as truly my ideas; their original conception, attribution and IP belongs to the authors of the SCP Wiki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/rumours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/rumours/</guid>
      <description>Please note that these rumours are not localised, local rumours are on their page.&#xA;A perpetual storm rages over the Cronemoor Swamp. A fell necromancer is releasing swarms of Undead Cats, which are spreading mischief and misinformation. The queen has been murdered by a red-robed assassin. The golem in the town square will answer questions, but only in riddles. A demonic cloud of howling flames has been summoned into the Briarwall Forest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/session-notes/session-notes-no1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/session-notes/session-notes-no1/</guid>
      <description>starting location: Brisburne Tavern man suspicious of two people leaving and coming back shortly after Some shadowy creatures/people cutting ties of boats, letting them drift</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/differences-regarding-factions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/differences-regarding-factions/</guid>
      <description>Thylyist Boons Attunement to all things mechanical Easy access to various military and economic resources Possibly acquiring Thylyian Military supplies legally or through conscription/service Drawbacks Narrative adjustments There‘s no world outside of Thylyist No Tech greater than gear, steam and steel Magic? doesn‘t exist&#xA;Kill-on-Sight orders from Dragonkin, Frisco and Exile/Nolka&#xA;Sepulchre Boons Sense of community; shared goods across the necropolis (i.e. less requirements for money) Diplomatic relations to Frisco Indirect access to both Thylyian and Friscoan Tech, Items and weaponry Access to the trains Drawbacks Treat/Property „Undying“ mandatory Prone to hollowing Outsider mentality and treatment by others Frisco Davern Exiled/Nølkā Kva’al </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/faction-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/faction-overview/</guid>
      <description>Empire of Thylyist Former city-state, grown to the size of a empire. The City of Thylyist is their capital, and epicentre of their official religion, the Followers of Mekhane, originally conceived as bunker-fort installation shortly before the end of the Nølkā-Mekhanite War. Their government is practically defunct. Instead, the religious elite (Council of Thylyist), and to a extend, the Gearforged Vanguard is de-facto ruling. The fanatical devotion impacts everyday life and has frozen technological and scientific progress, leaving them stuck in early steam-driven technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/locations-and-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/locations-and-you/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, foreigner.&#xA;Oh, what drives you around, into my humble domicile? Nevertheless, thou appear to seek answers to thy questions; who I shall provide. But to which crevice of the continent is your interest?&#xA;#TODO&#xA;Division The Continent Servilia is divided in five to six major regions, with two lesser. The Major regions include.&#xA;Long Savannah A large, flat stretch of land, which undergone a large climate shift after a natural fission reactor has surfaced and directed its thermal output upon the plains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/major-plotlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/major-plotlines/</guid>
      <description>#Structure #QUEST #Overviews&#xA;Greater Great Amnesty Close/Repair the Fountainhead Revenge Nølkā-Mekhanite War Coup Thylyist/Mekhanites Free the Ancients Free the Undying Lift the dogma about magic SOMETHING ABOUT THE DAVERN #TODO Revival Discover the SC-AM Project Restore the Argrosy Network Bring the Pseudoneo into the general awareness Spread true knowledge of The Lavish Empire and their Fall of the Lavish. Unity Make Peace between Thylyist-Frisco Bay Confederation Negotiate a treaty to the Twilit (for consented use) Bring The Cold and Crimson Heart together, allowing them to synergize Progress After Thylyist has been couped:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/religions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/religions/</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive summary of Cults, Organised Religions and other followings present in Servilia. Loosely sorted by impact and known member count.&#xA;Followers of Mekhane One of the two big religions ever formed in Servilia, this religion descended from the remnants of their once-great Mekhanite religion. Originally created as direct worshippers of Mekhanes will at the conception of Mankind, now turned into a lesser, deviated hodgepodge, in which their highest ranks assume the positions of dictatorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/species-of-servilia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/species-of-servilia/</guid>
      <description>#TODO ; WIP This page aims to provide comprehensive #Overviews of species known across Servilia.&#xA;Dragonkin Padian Shadowmaw A mostly nocturnal species with little representation in the Kva’al community. Oftentimes found living in isolation or off-limits, primarily around the astral ocean due to their nocturnal cycle matches with the nigh-constant nighttime of the ocean.&#xA;Ivory Highflyer Pseudoneo This peculiar collection of species has allegedly been created by the Lavish in their drive for expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/stressors-on-factions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/stressors-on-factions/</guid>
      <description>#Structure #Overviews This page aims to describe current issues that are inflicting trouble on the various factions and religions.&#xA;Empire of Thylyist Population Ongoing poverty, failing harvests, plummeting quality and standards of life. Absence of maintenance towards public interests such as trade routes, water infrastructure and security (i.e. protection from theft, burglary and assassinations) is giving raise to Organised Crime.&#xA;Additionally, the misery of citizens is feeding the New God of Fear and Hunger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/things-that-need-fixing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/things-that-need-fixing/</guid>
      <description>TODO 3: TOKYO DRIFT aka: big obstructions for readability towards «other people»&#xA;CONTEXT short overview of factions: Faction Overview Locations and You good, summarising index of major actors I.e. politicians, military, religious leaders, economical officials, … Character Overview Stressors on Factions = faction motivations why i am doing this -&amp;gt; Motivation Complete History of Servilia, since the entire history is busted and spread too widely Local Populace, Townsfolk Religions Universal Pantheon Cultural beliefs superstitions “Attributes” </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/universal-pantheon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/universal-pantheon/</guid>
      <description>Old Gods reign true, reign supreme. Archon (Outside of any boundaries, including time and space, universes. Capable of absolutely anything. Unaffected by followers, but might bestow powers upon followers.)&#xA;Yaldabaoth Voidfish Greater Deities that could possibly be the central pivot of a monotheistic religion; still influenced by follower belief and devoutness.&#xA;Fear and Hunger Charon Mekhane this is the todo area deity of time/fate, probably going with the three weavers of fate thread the creator the weaver the terminator/ender group of knowledge the one who reads the one who writes the one who archives/remembers/libraries Mischief </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/the-father-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/the-father-of-death/</guid>
      <description>The ancient deities figured out that death itself is not beatable or can be exploited, so they reached further and killed or lethally injured their father.&#xA;This caused death itself to become depressive and unable to perform their job as universal terminator, rendering all people afflicted with the curse of the undead.&#xA;Death itself is a fragment of Schi ut-Pula as it is central to any and all happenings on Schi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/weather-forecast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/weather-forecast/</guid>
      <description>Woes of the Twilit might influence tempests and clouds alike, occasionally creating bizarre weather phenomenon.&#xA;https://donjon.bin.sh/d20/weather/ Roll once per day&#xA;Medium Anomalous Weather</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
