<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Realms on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Realms on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/realms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/between/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/between/</guid>
      <description>The twisted and chaotic existence, shoved into the spaces between the compartments of the Twilit.&#xA;Nothing here follows anything; the laws of physics or reason are little more than a crude joke. Life is nigh impossible without fortitude and protection; lest exposed ones succumb to decay and warp, blame be the erratic ways of physics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/beyond/</guid>
      <description>The plane where all-encompassing, omnipotent deities, entities and concepts reside. Impossible to access by anyone who is not one of them. The name originally came from the fact that the Fountainhead cannot contain these entities, which earned them the title &amp;ldquo;beyond the exile&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Despite their infinite and incomprehensible power, these entities remain possible prey to those forces reaching beyond a single universe and its planes, those who scowl at the concept of a singular existence, those who will always exist, outside all time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/empire-of-shadows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/empire-of-shadows/</guid>
      <description>Overview Elemental plane of Darkness, under the reign of Her Majesty, the Queen of Shadows. Part to the Darkness domain, and thus neighbouring and fading into the The Void and Eternal Sea.&#xA;Lighting This plane is never lit, and sources of light are prone to consumption by the wispy shadows. Constantly shrouded in darkness, thus darksight/night vision/true sight is a necessity. Many of the local residents have developed other methods of orientation, such as echolocation or general darksight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/eternal-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/eternal-sea/</guid>
      <description>This Plane, or rather, parallel Realm, is the space within celestial bodies. It is not easily traversed, and hostile towards life. Few forays have been made into this space, and have proven very harsh and cost-expensive. The concept of reaching for the vast nothingness has been considered heretical, if not plain lunatic.&#xA;Defying terms of physics, this space refuses to be treated as three-dimensional space, but rather as infinite flat plane, emanating from wherever the observer attempts to foray into it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/the-void/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/dark-domain/the-void/</guid>
      <description>Note: This refers to the location, for the Entity associated, read Voidfish. At the bottom of the Twilit it lays, stretching into infinity. Due to the Fountainhead having torn its Borehole, it leaks into the material plane.&#xA;Supposedly only Vessels or hollows can stay here without being torn apart or going insane. Hollows quickly turn into vessels when contacting the Void.&#xA;The counteracting force to all that is matter, therefore archenemy to Schi ut-Pula and all other celestial entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/twilit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/planes/twilit/</guid>
      <description>Manifestation of Amarisk, coagulation of thought, condensed cognition. Source of energies and potential to mages and spellcasters through deliberate actions. Occasionally manifests Echoes and other supernatural phenomena, oftentimes scaping or rearranging a local landscape.&#xA;It is never directly seen, but its effects are always noticeable on the material plane.&#xA;Writhing in agony, tormented for eternity with its gross, rotting gore, with no healing in sight, all due to the Fountainhead. For this, it seeks vengeance against it’s^[read: the fountainheads] creators and origins, the Lavish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/scheties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/scheties/</guid>
      <description>Gas Dwarf. three major moons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/heaugi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/heaugi/</guid>
      <description>Moon of Schi. Tiny rocky core and mostly water and ice. A Lavish colony is suspected in these subsurface oceans. It emits a significant impact on the twilight continuum of Schi.&#xA;Forays through the twilit of Schi and Consultation with Heaugi ut-Tabānah have yielded&amp;hellip; not much. Horrors birthed through dread and anxiety dwell below the thick, but fragile icy shell. One Ocean, deeper than mankind&amp;rsquo;s machinery will ever reach. Dark. Cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/kynoly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/kynoly/</guid>
      <description>Moon of Schi. high volcanic activity and hot, presumably a captured protoplanet.&#xA;Heated from its wrath, its confusion and compensated dread of the whereabouts of its mother. A abandoned, freshly born child, filled with clueless rage, devoid of any options and left with many, too many, unanswered and unanswerable questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/opar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/opar/</guid>
      <description>A Moon of Schi. A rocky, desolate and cold moon, devoid of interesting features. &amp;hellip; or is it? Tied to Parop as the Seal of Man. Accompanied by Kynoly and Heaugi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/schi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/schi/</guid>
      <description>A earthen like planet, outfitted with rings and three moons:&#xA;Heaugi Opar Kynoly The only habitable planet in The Utuw Family. Was/is/will be home to several sentient and complex species.&#xA;0.13AU away from Utuw </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/02_northern-reaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/02_northern-reaches/</guid>
      <description>[Northern&#xD;Reaches]&#xA;Friday,&#xD;7. April 2023&#xA;09:51&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&#xA;Created with OneNote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/08_hallownest-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/08_hallownest-p/</guid>
      <description>Hallownest [P]&#xA;Monday,&#xD;25. April 2022&#xA;09:16&#xA;Meta-reference to&#xD;the entire scenery; is basically a&#xD;miniature copy of our realm with most features and similarity&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&#xA;Created with OneNote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/amida/numerator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/amida/numerator/</guid>
      <description>#Amida Big if not titanic organic and sentient supercomputers that search for a solution to the Curse of the Undead. Their entire structure houses a sector each, as they govern infrastructure. Numerators were able to interact with the control of the SC-AM project and tap the power output for Amida. Most of the heat produced is absorbed by purposed The Cold tissue to recuperate energy and not to devastate the environment like Rainworld.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/amida/sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/amida/sick/</guid>
      <description>%%SICK Illusions and Club Kink?%% %%Sinister Oasis of Kinky Delights?%% %%Sinful Indulgence Club &amp;amp; Kink%% The club-brothel-community in Amida-12, harbouring a very lax and liberal group of mutually-understanding nymphomaniacs and similar odd folks. The Avatar of A-12 is inclined towards SICK and therefore protects the organisation and its properties, albeit without much care.&#xA;This is where we live, turning sin into virtue, committing to the lifestyle. Give up your restraints, live your little life to it&amp;rsquo;s fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/davern-kingdom/davern-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/davern-kingdom/davern-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>#Faction A kingdom in a rather medieval state of development on transition to very very early tech (read: sophisticated agriculture), but already proficient in magic and other studies (present time). They are not driven towards technological and economical advancement due to an abundance of various arcane artefacts and relics and nationwide acceptance and teaching of the naturalist arts. This gives them a peculiar state of suspended development, as their artefacts and alike allow them to stay at their current state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/davern-kingdom/yawning-grave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/davern-kingdom/yawning-grave/</guid>
      <description>Buried asunder lie The Old Kings fleshy remains. Stripped off his bones, they remain chained to the throne. Left conscious, aware, missing their significant others parts, yet dreaming, yawning. Why is it sleeping? To dispel the churning thoughts and worries brought unto themselves? Placed into eternal hibernation, in the wait for the world? Laid dormant, eagerly awaiting a reunion with its skeleton? One daring enough may listen to the babbling of His corpse in its perpetual sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/archive-of-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/archive-of-old/</guid>
      <description>The Library sainted to all Shnūts of Time, and all deities of Knowledge. In this vast subterranean facility, all knowledge not stored elsewhere, everyone is welcomed to enter their own story into the central Lectern, from which your story is archived.&#xA;The Lectern is the central piece to anyone who does only want to place a entry or retrieve a single page fro/to the Archive. It is made from finest basalt, and engraved with a runic interface, which allows any user to request a blank page, and have a finished page sorted away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/central-thylyist-armoury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/central-thylyist-armoury/</guid>
      <description>#locations The main stockpile of the Thylyian Military and Sentinels.&#xA;You should be really carefully here, they don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone to see or know about this!&#xA;Headquarters to the Thylyian Military, and protected as such.&#xA;Threat Level: really fucking high (Creatures-Traps-Environment)&#xA;Suited Sentinels Off-Duty Soldiers Security Cameras Possible Loot: (Equipment-Valuables-Currency) Sentinel Power Armour (Full Set, x4) Baton+4 (x10) Sentinel Half Mask (x20) Location acquired from the Daeva or cradle. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/citadel-of-the-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/citadel-of-the-gear/</guid>
      <description>#Thylyist #Religion #locations The main religious building in Empire of Thylyist, sainted to Gear and Cogwork. Amongst the earliest buildings in Thylyist, dating back to the First Era.&#xA;Historical studies conducted in secret suggest that the citadel and the surrounding buildings originally functioned as tactical retreat and bunker installation to safeguard their arsenal and functional modules of Mekhane. Especially the wide-spanning Catacombs are heavily reinforced, as to withstand aeons of war raging above ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</guid>
      <description>Capital of the human population; highly advanced in mechanics and metalworking. However, they are strictly conservative, if not regressive, about more advanced technology due to their religious dogmata. The Archive within the lowest Levels feature the staggering history of Thylyist: they eradicated The Lavish Empire after abusing them to forcibly relocate the god-gone Nølkā. -&amp;gt; The Second Era Amida&amp;rsquo;s sector structure is derived from the fact that Thylyist already existed as megacity with several layers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/heart-of-mekhane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/heart-of-mekhane/</guid>
      <description>A large sphere of rotating gears and ticking escapements, crafted from brass and inscribed with glowing runes. No-one seems to know who created it, nor when, nor its purpose.&#xA;No tangible power source of this object is visible, and any kind of studies are met with highest force from the Followers of Mekhane as solely viewing it is considered heresy.&#xA;High Constructors believe that this piece is the heart of their torn apart god, the Blessed Machine Mekhane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/brisburne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/brisburne/</guid>
      <description>#locations #Settlements Second-largest city of Frisco Bay Confederation, and the bigger naval port and harbour than Frisco. Extremely rugged and shaped by the rough sailor folks that only temporarily reside there. An everchanging population due to being mostly, if not entirely, made up from travelling folk.&#xA;Despite their immense economic throughput and wealth, it appears that none of these revenues are utilised towards maintenance and expansion of the city, which leaves it to crumble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/duley-and-port/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/duley-and-port/</guid>
      <description>#Settlements #locations #Travel&#xA;Airport and Scientific Nexus in the Frisco Bay Duley and -Port is the scientific driver of the Frisco Bay Confederation and central to the region&amp;rsquo;s aerial transport.&#xA;It is known for its many open plazas and squares which are plated with bronze and other copper alloys, same as the rooves.&#xA;Many of these squares are long and rectangular, allowing smaller, winged aircraft to land and start from them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/frisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/frisco/</guid>
      <description>#Settlements #Faction The only other noteworthy human capital besides Thylyist, namesake to the Bay and Confederation. Originally founded by alive1 outcasts from Thylyist, they freed themselves from the nonsense of conservatism and doctrine, making them the de-facto leader in economic and scientific strength. Central railway node, since the Friscoan built most if not all of the Servilian Railroad and Train Network.&#xA;Economically strong due to being central to trade, travel and business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/the-cats-scriptorium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/frisco-bay/the-cats-scriptorium/</guid>
      <description>A large scribe&amp;rsquo;s workshop, served by a clowder of cats. The cats usually divide their time between playing, sleeping, and working on the pages of a book of omens and portents. If asked by a wizard, they may copy a spellbook or scroll, given the materials, but no more often than once per month. This business has proven fruitful, and several branch stores are under construction, as their services are excellent in terms of speed and quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/automated-remains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/automated-remains/</guid>
      <description>Various buildings and structures left around the continent by someone long gone. Most of them remain functional through the maintenance of peculiar critters and other creatures, which I did not inspect closer yet. In this entry I will summarise the most notable ones i found repeatedly, and theorise their function.&#xA;Gun Installation This impossible-to-deceive turret hoists one to four massive cannon barrels, each longer than a man, each with a bigger diameter of my head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/clocktowers-beneath-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/clocktowers-beneath-the-sea/</guid>
      <description>What now is known as the Isle of Tankar was once the peak of a mountain long forgotten, from eras far away, before land has reared its body. The first Mekhanites, the first ones to shape mass into design using power. Gears and springs, refined to perfection, made to endure, dragging their shambling remains into the present.&#xA;Rarely their distant sounds can be heard. We consider this an omen of something to whittle itself into existence, as the Lost Bells never carry good omens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/dump-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/dump-site/</guid>
      <description>A place where magicians and mechanists alike dumps their unused or misshaped creations. Location:&#xA;Dangerousness:&#xA;(Creatures-Traps-Environment)&#xA;No monsters Dysfunctional Spells and Machinery that can discharge Some wastes and chaos Actually a temporal anomaly that attracts waste and scrapped things through time Possible Loot:&#xA;(Equipment-Valuables-Currency)&#xA;Bag of puppies Glass cannon Bag of Crickets </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/inn-of-a-thousand-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/inn-of-a-thousand-names/</guid>
      <description>An elegant dwarven inn, which is said to have a thousand doors in a thousand towns, each under a different sign and name. Anyone who enters through a particular door can only leave through that same door, unless they know the innkeeper&amp;rsquo;s secret. Each house shares some similarities with the other houses, but not enough to differ from the local architecture and culture. Almost like secret codices allow for easy spotting of these inns and taverns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/lakehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/locations/lakehouse/</guid>
      <description>#locations #Ruin A big, chaotically built mansion, towering over the nearby lake. It emanates a warm and homely feel. Maybe you want to come inside?&#xA;Upon casting a spell or working magic within:&#xA;Something is off&amp;hellip; you don&amp;rsquo;t feel the usual exhaustion coming with magic. What was that? Did the floor panels just&amp;hellip; flap?&#xA;Built next and over to a small lake, with wooden struts and stone pillars holding the twined building stable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/</guid>
      <description>#Ancients #Areas&#xA;Area where transcended humanoids reside after getting contained by the Fountainhead through The Lavish Empire. Hollow Mountains were erected as earthbound containment wall.&#xA;Three notable/major settlements:&#xA;Londo Now ruined Anor New Londo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/floating-islands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/floating-islands/</guid>
      <description>#Areas Remnants of the Betrayal, overgrown and renatured shrapnel and rubble, coagulated by earthen spirits. Suspended by gatherings of aer (air) spirits, who create massive updraft winds to keep their homes adrift. Possibly the first manifestation of Terrain Shattered by the distress of the Twilit.&#xA;Well-protected by groups of Angels. Habitat to many different spirits, whom the Ancients foster and care about. Birthplace to manifested energies, who are aided by the Midwife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/limbo-boneyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/limbo-boneyard/</guid>
      <description>#Ancients #Void A big storage pile of Vessel Masks, carved from celestial and draconic bones, sealed away and heavily protected.&#xA;The Ancient Deities amassed Vessel Masks from failed or defeated Vessels to hinder the Void on affecting the material plane.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s located below Londo, dug by dwarves into the hollow mountains.&#xA;No one speaks about this, they either forgot or are too afraid of the word being spread. At some point, information got leaked and The Void caused a massive raid upon Londo with all available forces, which led to the destruction of Londo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/londo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/londo/</guid>
      <description>#Ancients #Settlements #Ruin The once-former co-capital of the Ancient Exile and entryway to the Limbo Boneyard. Coincidentally, the SC-AM Collision chamber is directly below it, which likely aided in attracting the Void&amp;rsquo;s raid.&#xA;It got overran and devastated by Vessels and Night Runners in a dramatic raid that incapacitated and crippled a lot of Ancients, including Darb ut-Tabānah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/streets-of-londo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/ancient-exile/streets-of-londo/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen the old man, in the closed-down market? Kicking up the paper, with his worn-out shoes?&#xA;(Londo)&#xA;#TODO do this thingamajig Have you seen the old man&#xA;In the closed down market&#xA;Kicking up the papers&#xA;With his worn out shoes?&#xA;In his eyes, you see no pride&#xA;Hand held loosely at his side&#xA;Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s paper&#xA;Telling yesterday&amp;rsquo;s news Have you seen the old girl&#xA;Who walks the streets of London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/hallownest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/hallownest/</guid>
      <description>%%Meta-reference to the entire scenery; is basically a miniature copy of our realm with most features and similarity %% Within the many caverns of the Hollow Mountains lies Hallownest, largest settlement to the Dwarves and many other, lesser creatures adapted to low-to-no-light conditions with minimal space. Tunnels dug, caverns excavated where rock is soft. This led to erratic structures, impossible to navigate to someone incapable of sensing the abundance of pheromone messaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/hollow-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/hollow-mountains/</guid>
      <description>The Lavish collaborated with the Council of Thylyist and constructed the Fountainhead to siphon the Twilit to raise these mountains, primarily to encase the remnants of the Nølkā. Secondarily, the terraforming has been used to raise the corners of the Palga Basin to provide more space to the thriving Lavish Empire. The Nølkā have effectively changed and shifted over time, and now are referred to as Ancients in their Exile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/searing-lode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/hollow-mountains/searing-lode/</guid>
      <description>Within the Hollow Mountains, Dwarves once struck groundwater, boiling and steaming to the touch. This led to the discovery of the %%Grand Heater Below, pending%%, easily being able to produce steam to drive dwarven forges and machining alike. Originally, the superheated water was discovered to connect through the Long Savannah up until through the Scorched Acres, where the Heart siphoned the heat. One most notable surface breach of this hot water running below are the Steam Gardens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/a-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/a-hill/</guid>
      <description>#locations&#xA;A hill that manifests on a random grassy plains once any full moon.&#xA;If one runs up that hill after the night it appeared, they can make a deal with &amp;ldquo;god&amp;rdquo;, to change the bodies of two NPCs or PCs.&#xA;Said to contain physical remnants of a deity or other powerful entity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/castle-on-a-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/castle-on-a-hill/</guid>
      <description>#Children-of-the-Flame #Ruin #dungeons #Cult&#xA;Running up A Hill, there it has a lonely castle, set to rot and salvage. It&amp;rsquo;s roofing, originally copper, has been completely torn out, and some sections have been demolished. Former Elvin stronghold, destroyed in the genocidal sweep of Thylyist against the Lavish. After the devastation of it and the surrounding areas, scavengers and pillagers tore out anything they could peddle away, leaving the stone brick walls towering like husks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/long-savannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/long-savannah/</guid>
      <description>#Regions Vast and extending plains, found to the northeast of the hollow mountains.&#xA;Former home to the Lavish, now known as the Wasteland.&#xA;Dry and arid, the opposite of the dense forest that covers the upper-left of Servilia. Old records speak of a flourishing rainforest, but only shrubs remain. The plantlife here is stubby, as if large, towering trees and bushes shrivelled up into miniatures.&#xA;Seemingly devoid of higher life, but few scientific expeditions have been made here yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/eroded-frames/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/eroded-frames/</guid>
      <description>#Ruin #Lavish&#xA;Old, derelict ruins of unknown architecture and materials, from within a deep basin.&#xA;You can sense some eerie sensation coming off it.. You are not welcome here.&#xA;Every part of these buildings is telling you to leave. Like a beloved one on the deathbed, wishing for a last silent moment.&#xA;Nearly everything has been raided and stripped down to the very raw frames. Where once were imposing, towering buildings are only crooked frames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/first-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/first-vault/</guid>
      <description>#dungeons Location: Salt Flats of The Wastes.&#xA;Approx. 5km northeast of the Fountainhead.&#xA;some rooms are outfitted with cryostasis capsules, most of which are opaque from rot or shattered.&#xA;Dangerousness: Lethal.&#xA;(Creatures-Traps-Environment)&#xA;Low level creatures, a few lost Hollow. Malevolent spirits and ghosts. Automated security systems, turrets, weak and rusty. Extreme environment level, but the vault provides shielding. High ionising radiation, bubbling chaos, lurks of void. Possible Loot:&#xA;(Equipment-Valuables-Currency)&#xA;Up to 60 HazMat Suits, full sets, slightly deteriorated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/fountainhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/fountainhead/</guid>
      <description>#Void #locations #Ruin&#xA;This is the interdimensional drilling rig that leads to Twilit and eventually, the void. The borehole is physically accessible. Once built as siphon to channel more energies from the Twilit into the material realm, designed to power all Arcane Engineering throughout the continent. It was later redone and enhanced to allow massive terraforming projects, which culminated in the Raising of the Hollow Mountains.&#xA;And now that the The Lavish Empire aren&amp;rsquo;t here to maintain the catalyst of the Fountainhead, the whole Between creatures (and -energies) come crawling through the wastes, corrupting the landscape and it&amp;rsquo;s residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/lavish-wastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/lavish-wastes/</guid>
      <description>#areas #Lavish&#xA;Was previously the capital of a nation of magic-affine molluscs, The Lavish Empire.&#xA;TODO: Rumours about The Wastes&#xA;Nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The plains of Lavish&amp;rdquo; by adventurers and alike&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Lavish&amp;rdquo; has succeeded as nickname.&#xA;After The Brotherhood Backstab, all water got evaporated and dried into salt, which got corrupted into Gliss by the lingering chaos and energies from the FH&#xA;They got nuked by the arcanophobes of Thylyist&#xA;No one except the Archives of Thylist knows about what happened here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/palga-basin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/palga-basin/</guid>
      <description>#Areas #Lavish&#xA;Location The Palga Basin was a once %%during the first era%% flooded basin and primary residence to the Lavish on Servilia (outside of the Sea Major). It got artificially flooded by the Lavish in the successful push to acquire ”land” and resources.&#xA;The basin, before it flooded, was a huge dust bowl with little life in it, most akin to a rocky desert. During the time it sheltered and housed the Lavish it was home to a flourishing and blooming oceanic ecosystem, which water drastically shaped the environment around it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/sc-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/sc-am/</guid>
      <description>#locations #Lavish&#xA;Super-collider Anti-matter power project Lavish-built super-collider with four major cylindrical towers for stabilisation Multitudes (256) of automated cooling ports placed around the ring, which pop up once a day to gather atmospheric nitrogen and dump accumulated heat → mysterious rock movement and heat deaths It&amp;rsquo;s still1 in operation and fully maintained by Pseudoneo entities, which are highly valued by scavengers The Automated Remains &amp;gt; Vents and towers are overgrown and concealed with rock, soil and plants, but they&amp;rsquo;re somewhat noisy (but most beings don&amp;rsquo;t perceive this noise yet avoid them still)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/syksa-lavish-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/syksa-lavish-capital/</guid>
      <description>tags: Lavish, Settlements, Locations The glorious metropolis of the Lavish Empire, home to most Lavish within Servilia. Settled in the middle of the Palga Basin, it harboured the Fountainhead and all that is Lavish, including the first experimental Argrosy (which faced refinement later on), the biological laboratories in which the Pseudoneo have been born, and more.&#xA;Buried deep below the surface lay forgotten bunkers, built for the anticipated cataclysm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/the-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/palga-basin/the-abyss/</guid>
      <description>The Pit into nothingness, a bottomless well-pit, through which only death and disease is conveyed. One daring might take the plunge, lest never return, never the same. It changes people. It changed the stretches of salt flats around it. Whoever dares to step beyond the edge is bound to perish. Or are they?&#xA;Entryway to the spaces beyond the material world; considered the mound of hell by many. Twisted into gruesome shapes from the writhing agony and pain-made-matter of the Twilit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/scorched-acres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/scorched-acres/</guid>
      <description>Stretches of desert, shaped by the Crimson Heart. Once grassland like its parent, the Long Savannah, for it has been dried and burnt by the flames. Little plants remain, those surviving bent from and to the everlasting cinders omnipresent throughout the unkind sandy stretches.&#xA;Some sand has been baked and fused into alien glass formations, pillars and spires. Catching the sunlight, they paint a spectacle unbeknownst to the stranger’s view, but also blinding an unwary eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/sentinel-of-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/long-savannah/sentinel-of-steel/</guid>
      <description>As if a corpse was poorly buried, with its partly rotten partly torn off limbs and skin shown in unsightly ways and pose. Stagnant, yet suspended and dormant it lies there. Partially aware, partially deceased. Formerly a colossus who&amp;rsquo;d flatten entire cities at a mere tap; the zenith of Mekhane&amp;rsquo;s Design Abused. Becrept, befallen with it&amp;rsquo;s archenemy, suffering a same fate, reduced into vermin: the red plague.&#xA;[!WARNING] AI slop Amidst the rugged landscape, a solemn monument to a bygone era stands as the remnants of a defunct war machine once deployed by the Mekhanites in their relentless conflict against the Nolka.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/caverns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/caverns/</guid>
      <description>#Areas Imagine a sprawling deep underground network of small, room sized cavities. Some of them are barren, raw rock and devoid of all life, whereas other as are filled with moss, luminescent fungi, and other exotic specialist life forms that exist underground, Occasionally, these cavities even bear a range of valuable fancy minerals and rocks.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s certain that these caves have formerly been inhabited by at least one intelligent species, as we found rotten wood struts, leftovers of fibre and metal scraps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/court-of-storms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/court-of-storms/</guid>
      <description>The Court to Tombstone, where faith is decided upon. Arches resemble a spacious ceiling, stone paves the floor in elaborate patterns. Upon a elevated podium resides The One Who Judges and the Masked Ones. Eroded, withered copper spires form the corners and pillars of the flooring, conducting electricity from the thunderclouds residing above. Eleven and twenty pedestals seat the judges, five for the judged, may their verdict be righteous and swift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/green-swale-of-seven-spires/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/green-swale-of-seven-spires/</guid>
      <description>The lush heart of the forested hell that is the Ninth Forest. Around the indented basin-lake tower seven spires, adorned with vines and tangles. The basin-lake is the beginning and end of many rivers and streams throughout the Ninth Forest, some of which extend underground.&#xA;Well-guarded by raised, enclosing cliff faces, who raise suspicion about natural formation. Certainly peculiar creatures reside here, most of which pose significant threats and risks towards unsuspecting or inexperienced travellers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/lost-city-of-the-ninth-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/lost-city-of-the-ninth-forest/</guid>
      <description>During The First Era: A flourishing and thriving city, dedicated towards research and trade. A joint effort and collaboration between the Lavish, Dragonkin and Humanity gave way for a ultimate creation: a draconic-blooded humanoid, augmented with Pseudoneo biotechnology, who have dubbed themselves Varuú. This city was the one to be gifted the first Argrosy station, which remains functional. Given the diverse cultural mix present, it is considered necessary to go vertical, both into the ground and into the skies, to accommodate all residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/ninth-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/ninth-forest/</guid>
      <description>A wide-spanning forest ecosystem, including rain-forest but also temperate towards Mediterranean plant life.&#xA;Central to it is the Green Swale of Seven Spires. Officially termed Ninth Forest due to it’s position on the clock, if the continent would be abstracted into a clock. Colloquially dubbed &amp;ldquo;Jungle of Megaliths&amp;rdquo; due to many massive rocky spires scattered throughout, whose origins or purpose remain unknown and forgotten.&#xA;Most of the coast to this forested region has developed into a independent, yet adjacent ecosphere, the Lunar Mangroves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/sepulchre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/sepulchre/</guid>
      <description>The undying City #Undead #Settlements #Faction&#xA;The main settlement 1 for victims of the Curse of the Undead.&#xA;Only a smaller fraction of the residents voluntarily lives here, most of them got forcibly sent here, oftentimes through concentration camp-like treatment from certain governmental bodies.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s underground, and they have a small religion going on, but it drifted too far into states that a alive and integer mind cannot parse. +1d4 insanity on inspect The main place of worship of their religion is said to be built atop a Lichen relic vault, which has been cemented there before the Great Woe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/alp-peaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/alp-peaks/</guid>
      <description>#Areas #Northern-Reaches These peaks seem to be haunted by poltergeists and memetic nightmares, but only during night. This may be a influence from the deviated sea. An above average occurrence of night runners have been spotted here&amp;hellip; Almost identical to the surface traits of the Hollow Mountains:&#xA;Infested with night Runners Multitude of sharp mountain peaks Related to a supernatural being. However, the Night Runner presence looms much stronger here, as no other force is governing them here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/black-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/black-forest/</guid>
      <description>#Areas The colony of what little remains from the decimated plant life that once resided on the Northern Reaches.&#xA;This forest is settled around the feet of the Alp Peaks. Mainly consisting of needle trees, and being entangled with many (partly subterranean) rivers causes a high occurrence of deadwood and therefore drive a flourishing ecosphere of the extreme, for those that accustomed to the weather and cold. The canopy is very opaque, depriving the forest floor of almost any light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/eternal-glacier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/eternal-glacier/</guid>
      <description>#Areas This glacier poses a temporal anomaly, as anything within its area appears frozen to outside observers. Still, being a glacier, it grinds down its way, eventually into the ocean, where the anomalous effects begin to fade and eventually cease.&#xA;Nevertheless, a colossal spire of the hardest rock splits some arm or branch of the glacier, which shapes a massive icy plain, which isn&amp;rsquo;t subjected to the glacial movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/ice-plains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/ice-plains/</guid>
      <description>The stretch where Heart of Cold is situated.&#xA;Nothing but blinding, glaring white in sight. This is hell, frozen over. It still wants you dead, at every step you take.&#xA;There, there is the wall. The stockades, raised to protect It. Stone, taken from mountains, stolen from riverbeds, entrenched into plastered growths of ice and mineral. It lives its solitude, for intruders, like you, are not desired. They are merely feed, fodder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/northern-reaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/northern-reaches/</guid>
      <description>#Regions&#xA;The area of a slightly displaced polar cap. Home to the Empire of Winds and The Cold.&#xA;Typically perpetually covered in snow and always arctic cold (ca. -20 to -40°C).&#xA;Extremely harsh environment conditions, hence why the Empire of Wind and its &amp;ldquo;citizens&amp;rdquo; is the predominant species.&#xA;This region is heavily influenced by the now-dead volcanism and the everlasting cold.&#xA;Most significant are towering Alp Peaks, which add the unique climatic aspect by blocking off winds from the sea, a distant and deviated arm of the Astral Ocean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/tundra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/northern-reaches/tundra/</guid>
      <description>#Areas #Northern-Reaches&#xA;Outside of the harsh rocks and ice, there is a far extending tundra, which is frozen with permafrost even in seemingly illogical stretches. The temperature there tends to vary per-region, and some lines tend to be notably colder. Based on the proximity to the Heart of Cold, these temperature shifts might be effects of its accursed veins running below the surface. Sometimes, the veins are seen, as the despicable conduits break through the surface, encased in clearest ice, cold enough to ensnare one&amp;rsquo;s breath whole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/astral-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/astral-ocean/</guid>
      <description>#Regions This ocean is a gem in itself. Any blockade in seeing the dark waters above is counter-obscured and makes access to starry skies possible at any time, even during the day. It is commonly assumed that this Ocean extends beyond what we know and into the skies above.&#xA;This region is seemingly capable of reading minds and works as telescope and magnifier to show figures and constellations to symbolises something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/belisha-beacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/belisha-beacon/</guid>
      <description>A beacon and lighthouse, built atop one of the many scattered islands of Servilia. It&amp;rsquo;s original architects are speculated to be Lavish workforces, but results of analysis opens speculations for it to be older than the First Era. Few sorcerers and magi have been there, but those have reported sensational findings and energies. Rudimentary Radio Equipment has caught signals from it, which often manifest as beeps and blips. We&amp;rsquo;re not sure what information these signals carry, but we&amp;rsquo;re working on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/chromatic-calderas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/chromatic-calderas/</guid>
      <description>Part of the Astral Ocean #Regions, subdivision of Kaá-Rav.&#xA;The ocean spans over the edges of multiple tectonic plates, and therefore has a high volcanic and geologic activity. This shaped a high number of atolls and still-active volcanoes, and those atolls and islands feature astounding numbers of geysers, hot springs and alike. A certain series of volcanoes and calderas is doused in abundance of mineral-sourced colours.&#xA;These bear a special trait: Observing a specific one being active causes a outburst of specific emotions in the observer, the emotions being associated to the observed colour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/city-of-stargard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/city-of-stargard/</guid>
      <description>Overview A community of isolated and deranged sorcerers who devote their time towards the study and use of celestial bodies and formations. A decent part of their population is made from other outcasts and strangers.&#xA;The only remaining actively practising guild for Astral Sorcery. Townsfolk and activity are only seen past sundown and cease after sunrise; during the day, every citizen sleeps until nightfall. There are only few accommodations and housing-for-hire that offer a &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; opening schedule for foreigners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/forgotten-atoll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/forgotten-atoll/</guid>
      <description>#TODO&#xA;Not too far away from the Chromatic Calderas is a cluster of atolls, which are common residence to Antares. This area is differing from the rest of the ocean itself, as only dead and distant stars (from outside the milky way) shine. This usually confuses seafarers who orient themselves on constellations.&#xA;Additionally, the atoll easily obscures one&amp;rsquo;s mind, lightly acting as anti-memetic effect.&#xA;It is said that this area has been neglected by The Navigator due to the absence of common constellations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/ka%C3%A1-rav/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/ka%C3%A1-rav/</guid>
      <description>#Areas A former rift in tectonic plates caused this jagged chain of volcanoes to tower over the vast ocean.&#xA;Dubbed &amp;ldquo;left ribs of the world&amp;rdquo; due to it&amp;rsquo;s regularly spaced peaks, which seem to arch slightly.&#xA;Lesser volcanoes turned into Atolls and other smaller islands, who are mostly barren and harsh towards settlers. Their volcanic origin and marine erosion created several larger cavities, which now shelter renegades, pirates and similar shady folks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/lunar-gateways/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/lunar-gateways/</guid>
      <description>Three arches, forming a triangle. One from dark basalt, hot to the touch. One from blueish ice, frozen forever. One from white rock, pock-scarred.&#xA;Speculations believe that these arches are gateways made from and leading to each moon, made from their rock and mass gifted to mankind by a deity beyond. Stepping into the space of the triangle is forbidden as it is considered sacred. Each of these archways seem completely resilient to force, and attempting to moving them has proven futile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/skalitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/skalitz/</guid>
      <description>#Settlements Per-Forma capital of dragonkin, situated in the central region of Kaá-Rav. Humanoid visitors are rare around here, those few reports from ages ago described a vast, widely spread village of primarily stone built single storey buildings. Rumours have said for Skalitz to be in possession of several sacred Alder trees, such as as that one inhabited by Leonis around the end of the First Era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/the-oculus-of-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/the-oculus-of-night/</guid>
      <description>Close to the centre of Stargard, this dome resides with a circular opening at its centre, supported by a ring of caryatid columns. The sky seen through the oculus is perpetually dark, marked by strange, foreign constellations of stars. Through intricate mechanisms, the entire dome can shift and turn, changing its viewport towards other sections of the sky. During day, the &amp;ldquo;eyelids&amp;rdquo;, two hemispheres, close over the dome through a unseen force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/the-tellurion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/the-tellurion/</guid>
      <description>The machine for predicting, and possibly altering, orbits. It remains unfinished, or never was finished to begin with.&#xA;Central to Stargard, but left tampered and dysfunctional. Its many gears whine and wail on every occasion, subject to seemingly eternal deadlock. None of the local residents have been able to understand the inner workings of this machination nor it&amp;rsquo;s driving force, despite several associations and societies forming solely to unveil the mystique at play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/lunar-mangroves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/lunar-mangroves/</guid>
      <description>Overview This Mangrove forest is never seen during day. It is always obscured by a almost tangible fog during daytime, which clears at nightfall. When it has cleared, observers on the ground witness a astonishing view to the sky, specifically the moons.&#xA;Regional Context The mangrove trees themselves act as tidal dampeners, to protect the Ninth Forest and its fragile ecosystem from the erratic tides of the Astral Ocean. The mangroves span a notable majority of the forest&amp;rsquo;s coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/edge-of-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/edge-of-hope/</guid>
      <description>#Regions The &amp;rsquo;edge&amp;rsquo; of the known and mapped world. Referred to as The Edge of Hope since no-one who ventured further returned ever since, including dragon scouts and airships.&#xA;This Region marks the seam of the Servilian tectonic plate, covering Kaa&amp;rsquo;rav and the isle of Northern Reaches.&#xA;Possibly obscured by fog and extreme weather like dense thunderclouds. It appears that these may not be of a natural cause, potentially [worth investigating](Edge Kraken).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/sea-major/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/sea-major/</guid>
      <description>#Regions The ocean that stretches the entire known world. Transitions into the Astral Ocean around the northwest coast of Servilia.&#xA;Flavour Text: &amp;ldquo;Alone, at the edge of a universe, humming a tune. For merely dreaming we were [Snow]&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&#xA;A stretched out area of islands, home to all other dragons that don&amp;rsquo;t reside in and around the Hollow Mountains (and spine of the world). The central island group Kaá-Rav features a series of mountain peaks, as the other end of the massive proposed rib cage to the spine of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/sphill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/sphill/</guid>
      <description>0,66AU Distance to Schi, is large and rocky. Does not have any atmosphere. Minerals are primarily of the cyclosilicate and orthosilicate family, with a wild blend of non-silicates taking the remainders.&#xA;Sphill has 55 moons, which are evenly spaced around the planet across the vertices of a hypothetical icosphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/st.-nowhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/st.-nowhere/</guid>
      <description>We are here because you are not. Wait, how are you reading this if you cant be here? Here at the end of time we are, and we don’t really know why. Someone thought it’d be amusing to see a group of stragglers try to reverse time or something. We might look like gods, but trust me, compared to them we are nothing. Vermin at best. Oh well, we got used to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/the-utuw-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/the-utuw-family/</guid>
      <description>Utuw K-Main sequence, habitable zone 0.1228 AU - 0.1771 AU @0.7 solar masses + 0.8× solar radius, 40&#39;856 bil years old&#xA;Schi 0.13AU earthlike ringed inhabited Opar desolate rocky (moon) Kynoly volcanic, heated, captured protoplanet Heaugi icy, frozen, cold 0,66AU Distance to Schi, is large and rocky. Does not have any atmosphere. Minerals are primarily of the cyclosilicate and orthosilicate family, with a wild blend of non-silicates taking the remainders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/three-moons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/three-moons/</guid>
      <description>Three Children burdened upon their Mother, One to be firey and filled with wrath and hatred, One to be left alone, forgotten and left to drown in tears, One to be made without character, defined by nothing and absence.&#xA;In the absence of their Mother, the three children struggle with their abandonment, each filled with sorrow and fear. All of them are alone, yet none of them seek company through their siblings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/utuw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/utuw/</guid>
      <description>The star of the aptly named system. K-Main sequence, habitable zone 0.1228 AU - 0.1771 AU @0.7 solar masses + 0.8× solar radius, 40,856 billion earth years old.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
