<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somewhat Coherents on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Somewhat Coherents on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/deployed-giant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/deployed-giant/</guid>
      <description>Gunfire ringing in my ear, bullets hailing from above. The whistling, ear-shattering noise, then the impact. Everyone scuttles about, as if someone prodded a stick into an anthill, looking for bodies to recover. But there was nothing but smoulders and red smears where the shell hit. Seconds after, the cacophony of gunfire, screams and explosions resumes. In the distance, unnoticed so far, strides a colossus of steel, determined to change the tide of it all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/on-the-victorious-defeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/on-the-victorious-defeat/</guid>
      <description>So, it ends. It finally found something worthy of it&amp;rsquo;s shell, the bittersweet feelings of emerging victorious after countless losses and defeats. The machine has been bested, beaten. The cacophony of destruction and war, which it orchestrated, put to a end. Now it&amp;rsquo;s rigid, inert hull, half buried, silently watches over the landscape, it&amp;rsquo;s innards gutted, unable to react or process anything.&#xA;But it is not the last of it&amp;rsquo;s kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/posthumous-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/posthumous-unity/</guid>
      <description>The machine rejects the flesh, lest it knows the flesh intents to stay. United and one after defeat to one another they lie dormant, discordant towards each other. The flesh has found its new shell; the stability and strength of alloy is promising, unlike its former vessel of grotesquely shaped skin and bones and carapaces. The machine has lost itself, slowly accepting its new innards, for the olden guts been stolen and peddled away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/reddened-warmachine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/reddened-warmachine/</guid>
      <description>Now, there they are, in Posthumous Unity. United, recovering from the wounds and grave damage inflicted to another. Half-buried, the mechanical colossus grew armour, bloodied plates of bone and chitin. Sought out to revenge the cruelty and recklessness they both experienced during their life. Soon, they shall emerge from the soil and stride the lands once more, hunting down those who brought them their misery.&#xA;Nothing but the very thing that struck down the machine is the same that gives rise to the ancient frames&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/the-tale-of-two-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/war-and-flesh/the-tale-of-two-giants/</guid>
      <description>A machine, made to vanquish the indomitable human spirit. A monster, birthed to usurp all there is. Two unstoppable forces, made to face another, fighting for resolution of their quest. In the last glimpse, as their inner workings start to fail from the damage inflicted by the other, both become one in a dying embrace. Their suffering leaves suffering, yet to be released from their abuse as tools. Tools, created by cowards, who nudge around machinations and abominations on boards with long pointy sticks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021021-58-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021021-58-29/</guid>
      <description>Pillars of steel, concrete and mystery, reaching into the foul sky. Monoliths, each bigger than you can perceive and understand. Surrounded by the harsh, chemical stench of a industrial complex, you stand in front of a gap, only held back by a flimsy, rusted railing. The abyss calls for you, the railing is weak. Lost you are, stuck in paralysis, unable to decide or act. Is it really worth it, living, slaving away, at the promise of eventual relief that you know you&amp;rsquo;ll never reach?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021022-39-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021022-39-35/</guid>
      <description>The veil of fog below, I want to pierce it. What are they hiding in there? But you, yes, things have changed. We now have wings. Fouling ones, at that, but we can try. The railing is a easy obstacle to throw. The railing is ripped out of it&amp;rsquo;s aged sockets and bolts, and now falling down the gap. It is out of sight now. Will we make the jump? Pacing about on the catwalk, no longer guarded by a allusion of safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/these-foul-spires/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/these-foul-spires/</guid>
      <description>These foul spires, intertwined with their wicked veins. Who knows what they&amp;rsquo;re hiding in these? What forsaken abominations are being enslaved to be our very sustenance? Everything here revolves around them, they define our nation and society. Irregular and twisted like bricks being stacked another recklessly and held together by these abominable arteries. And the light. The lighting follows you everywhere, there is not a single crevice left undone. Glaring and over-saturated do the advertisements scream for attention.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
