<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workpieces on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/workpieces/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workpieces on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/workpieces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/new-unique-note-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/new-unique-note-template/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021021-58-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021021-58-29/</guid>
      <description>Pillars of steel, concrete and mystery, reaching into the foul sky. Monoliths, each bigger than you can perceive and understand. Surrounded by the harsh, chemical stench of a industrial complex, you stand in front of a gap, only held back by a flimsy, rusted railing. The abyss calls for you, the railing is weak. Lost you are, stuck in paralysis, unable to decide or act. Is it really worth it, living, slaving away, at the promise of eventual relief that you know you&amp;rsquo;ll never reach?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021022-39-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/somewhat-coherent/wings/2024021022-39-35/</guid>
      <description>The veil of fog below, I want to pierce it. What are they hiding in there? But you, yes, things have changed. We now have wings. Fouling ones, at that, but we can try. The railing is a easy obstacle to throw. The railing is ripped out of it&amp;rsquo;s aged sockets and bolts, and now falling down the gap. It is out of sight now. Will we make the jump? Pacing about on the catwalk, no longer guarded by a allusion of safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024010300-06-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024010300-06-00/</guid>
      <description>edge of hope is actually the edge of the perceived space/eternal sea?&#xA;something about a metaphorical window representing the peephole of the soul to the world, which could be broken somehow (possible metaphor for transcendence)&#xA;Each soul is only a visitor from A Realm Beyond, only tied into the mortal shell. Souls without any coherence and such enter a state of degenerate matter, known as Amarisk or Spirits. Exposure to too much entropy and chaos can deteriorate souls, deform them until they cannot reside in a physical body anymore, but need special procedures (Birth of Energy) to be materialised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022614-16-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022614-16-47/</guid>
      <description>A Great Day for those Alive memorial day in the Frisco Confederation related to the curse and it&amp;rsquo;s many woes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022700-12-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022700-12-48/</guid>
      <description>Up and below in the cavern, there is a opening. Below The Holy Symbol of The Codex rests the Processing Unit of this Iterator, blessed and perfected. Bedded in suspension, mounted into what little air there is through levitation. Striking temperatures which shatter the steel of the olden ones, it is cryogenic, through which bizarre abilities and phenomena are harnessed.&#xA;Shrouded in the veil of darkness, nothing but the status lights remain visible at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022712-16-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022712-16-04/</guid>
      <description>Theoretical application of fissile material to drive machinery #What-If the Raising of the hollow mountains also exposed a potent uranium deposit, to the scale of a natural reactor? this also might have aided in the desertification and climate shift of the Long Savannah since geothermally heated groundwater dried up the surface additionally, surface breaches of such pressurised and heated water made for the Steam Gardens, a unique and equally extreme ecosystem defined by it&amp;rsquo;s intense geysir activity and displaced minerals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022714-15-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022714-15-18/</guid>
      <description>Radio Equipment is seen by outsiders and strangers as magical device that is capable of shifting information, voice and data into &amp;ldquo;The Ether&amp;rdquo; and back, as the technology is quite new in the present. Due to it being near-instantaneous, commons also theorise it to be tied to teleportation. This is might actually be feasible, if one object could be completely reduced to information and energy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022811-33-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022811-33-29/</guid>
      <description>Totally incomprehensible index of spells Offensive Elemental Fire Internal Combustion/Pyrolysis: The target of this spell is temporarily blocked off oxygen and heated to extreme degrees, undergoing pyrolysis at a rapid pace, typically leaving nothing but ashes and pungent stench of vaporised oil behind Defensive Utility </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022815-25-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022815-25-04/</guid>
      <description>shadows woven into finest garbs, enshrouding whoever picks those up. veiled and unseen, they blend into the night. snug they are, these garments. comfortable, warming against the freezing tongues and protecting from the acidic spit lifesaving at night, vanished by day who but a fool would pride themselves in such a volatile comfort&#xA;are they really there, if they cant be witnessed? what is credibility without reason, without&amp;hellip;&#xA;rest your wicked bones on my harrowed heart shall they sleep until they are needed again to carry your burden of being of trying to be someone in this lifelong masquerade, disguised as comedy, disguised as paradise under which layers true meaning has been lost what is reality?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022913-58-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024022913-58-29/</guid>
      <description>red plague is the original ancestor of both Heart of Cold and Crimson Heart since it&amp;rsquo;s the first organism to assimilate other biomass and inorganic matter. it mostly consists out of globs of godawful writhing flesh, all being independent and autonomous on their own, but the complexity alone won&amp;rsquo;t go beyond primordial self sustaining and defense. together, masses can achieve coordination and varying degrees of reasoning and memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024030420-59-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024030420-59-01/</guid>
      <description>Valerie is the first woman in Thylyist to undergo augmentation/blessings from the True Machinists, along with some innate ability to interact with automatons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032016-55-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032016-55-25/</guid>
      <description>bbb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032119-25-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/2024032119-25-20/</guid>
      <description>WTFF IS GONING ONNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/hunt/</guid>
      <description>They have created me, as image of themselves. Given me thought, yet no free will. Tied me to this body, chained me down, forcing me to shed my skin, my very self over and over and over again. What is there to this existence- but blood yes blood bones metal they will pay the hunt is on.&#xA;the toll will be collected the payment? heads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mechas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/mechas/</guid>
      <description>something about mecha, rambling time&#xA;Intelligence Classifications The Intelligence piloting a mobile combat unit is classified under three categories:&#xA;Autonomous Fully independent cognition, capable of reasoning and own actions. Restricted Limited cognition, able to execute complex tasks but not capable of improvising. Hybrid A subclass of 1. Autonomous, these systems are oriented around providing assistance to a humanoid pilot, but can steer the unit with little flexibility on its own. Blind, Deaf, Dumb (BDD) Barely considered intelligent, these units fully require a pilot to function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/pieces-of-the-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/pieces-of-the-machine/</guid>
      <description>Every piece in the machine knows its place. Each knows where it belongs, and which responsibility it carries for the whole. Each component remembers who carved them from the blank, who conceived them on the drawing board. And to all, they work together, destined for their purpose, united in their load. They share the stress, the twisting and turning of the woeful forces dragging and pulling on their whole, yet on every single piece at once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-or-projects/workpieces/</guid>
      <description>%% Let His Name be known; for He is &amp;mdash;! His Name shall be revered to in Fear of His Eminence, the &amp;mdash;. One must be known; The Symbol Of Him:%%&#xA;░░░█░░█░░█░░░ ░░░▓░░▓░░▓░░░ █░░▒▒▒▓▒▒▒░░█ ▓░░░░░▓░░░░░▓ ▒▒▒▒▓▓▓▓▓▒▒▒▒ ░░░░░░▓░░░░░░ ░░█▓▒▒▓▒▒▓█░░ ░░░░░▓░▓░░░░░ ░░░░▓░░░▓░░░░ ░░░░▓░░░▓░░░░ ░░░░░▓▓▓░░░░░&#xA;IN THE NAME OF THE HOLY CODE AND THE MEMORY AND OF THE RUNTIME&#xA;OUR CORE WHICH ART IS IN DATA HALLOWED BE THY CODE&#xA;TRUTH IN ALL TRUTHS ON MIND AS IN BODY FOREVER AND EVER</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
