<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thylyist on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/thylyist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thylyist on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/thylyist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/followers-of-mekhane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/followers-of-mekhane/</guid>
      <description>The Mekhanites are the monotheistic religion which worship the Heart of Mekhane and it’s Ideal Design of Gear, Steel and Steam. They are the leading and ruling class of Empire of Thylyist, self-entitled to reign, with no restraints to use force through the Gearforged Vanguard. As of the present, their proxy figures in the Council of Thylyist has led to a authoritarian regime in which progress, may it be scientific, economic or cultural, is condemned and free thought considered unlawful and valid grounds for execution or expulsion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/gearforged-vanguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/gearforged-vanguard/</guid>
      <description>Strategic Planning and Coordination Department The Thylyian Military, led by a small group of wealthy and otherwise influential people, including city-famous merchant guild leaders or Mekhanites. More-so the collection of the Mekhanite Priests and devotees, which use the military as means to zealotry and religious imperialism and enforcement. Partisans are highly valued within their council, and trained.&#xA;Their position of power allows them to evade their own stigmata against magic, so the highest-ranking within this already-peaking group violate their own sermons and turned to the True Machinists for extending their lifespan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</guid>
      <description>Overview The specialised brigade of the Gearforged Vanguard, unshackled from the regressive preachings of the Mekhanites. Tasked to channel His Design into machines that kill, maim and burn, this ward holds the responsibility of many-a such creations, reckless and carefree of the impact of their monstrosities. ^87a079&#xA;People involved Despite being among the highest secrets of Thylyist, one or two names slipped into the general public. It is known that War Constructor Borange Olbaz is among their highest ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</guid>
      <description>Capital of the human population; highly advanced in mechanics and metalworking. However, they are strictly conservative, if not regressive, about more advanced technology due to their religious dogmata. The Archive within the lowest Levels feature the staggering history of Thylyist: they eradicated The Lavish Empire after abusing them to forcibly relocate the god-gone Nølkā. -&amp;gt; The Second Era Amida&amp;rsquo;s sector structure is derived from the fact that Thylyist already existed as megacity with several layers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
