<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Items on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/items/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Items on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/items/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/eldritch-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/eldritch-brand/</guid>
      <description>The brand of the Voidfish, slowly carving out the unfortunate body it has been placed upon. It oozes, which seems to attempt to lash onto anything it grabs. The ooze, black as night, darker than anything.&#xA;This should be the key to the Limbo Boneyard.&#xA;When carrying, the image of the Great Old One will engrave itself into the user, giving +2 fixed insanity after 1 week in game.&#xA;This mental branding is building a immunity (50%) to future insanity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/fountainhead-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/fountainhead-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>#Item The massive construct inserted into The Fountainhead, required for sustained operation.&#xA;Consists of many exotic materials and is highly fragile, care is advised.&#xA;It looks like a long cylinder, two to three men high and inscribed with arcane runes.&#xA;Magical Attunenent: Perceiving this object of immense power makes your powers squirm with fear.&#xA;A strange smell and whizz is in the air&amp;hellip; (ozone creation from the highly potent technomagy)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/horn-of-blizzards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/horn-of-blizzards/</guid>
      <description>The wind is blowing on these cold, cold grounds. My boots are a-roaming on these cold, cold lands. From every mountain peak that I see echoes off the horn. May the Empire of Winds keep us safe and sound. Are we worthy of the empire of winds? The storms are overwhelming, but we keep on climbing, In order to be worthy of the empire of winds! My Ears are hurting, but we keep on pushing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/mask-fragment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/mask-fragment/</guid>
      <description>#Void #Item&#xA;When brought together, any amount of these will fuse together into a full Vessel Mask, with the seams being filled with the raw abhorrent energy it is driven by (typically taking a red-deep purple swirling shape). A vessel may take this cluster of irregular masks to increase it&amp;rsquo;s HP by amount of shards in the cluster*5+1d4×mask shards Found in the proximity of the Fountainhead and floating directly in the Void.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/mekhanite-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/mekhanite-staff/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Weapon #Mekhanites #Religion Staff&#xA;Origin: Mekhanite. This item was created by devoted followers of Followers of Mekhane, the Broken God, consisting of mechanisms and gearwork. It was created by the Thylyian Department of Construction. It is forged from beryllium bronze and HSLA steel, and it incorporates gears and other mechanical parts. Its powers are extremely predictable and reliable (often not requiring a roll for abilities that normally do), and might relate to constructs or creating order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/overly-fancy-milkbag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/overly-fancy-milkbag/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Component&#xA;Sold by the milkman, high grade milk&#xA;Can be used for alchemy&#xA;Good healing item</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/premature-heart-of-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/premature-heart-of-cold/</guid>
      <description>A small heart, consisting out of mostly indiscernible mass, and frozen necrotic tissue and biomass.&#xA;It seems to chill the air around it, covering itself with ornate ice crystals. Inspecting these crystals instils a sense of dread in the observer.&#xA;Someone must have taken a tissue sample from the Cold, which shaped itself into this intriguing heart.&#xA;Upon contact with the body of any higher organism, may it be dead or alive, it spreads out tendril-like veins, starting to bury itself in the body, shuffling the insides without care to replace the heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/red-telephone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/red-telephone/</guid>
      <description>#Item A red dial-up telephone with a spiral corded receiver. It appears to not have any connections or cable plugs whatsoever aside one for the receiver. Every Morning at 7:30, it rings. If picked up, a frenzied voice attempts to communicate something in hectic mannerisms of a unknown language. Only shortly after, the initial caller is soon overpowered by a deep resonating hum, which one will feel in their bones. It won’t take long until this hum is overwhelming and one feels forced to hang up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/reliquary-of-false-promises/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/reliquary-of-false-promises/</guid>
      <description>Powerful objects, made as fanciful hook, line and sinker, do drag down below the fools, the unwise and the greedy. Power, wealth and other promises float and flicker on the surface, leading to the trap, one which eventually turns fatal. Promises be granted, lest they take their price in rates of interest, turning, twisting the one who fell for it. One who wants to ring the bells may do so with the striker, but only once, for it will consume them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/seed-of-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/seed-of-thought/</guid>
      <description>#QUEST Quest Item.&#xA;Player Description: A seemingly inert seed from a tree within the Ancient Exile. When held: you imagine how a tiny leaf could sprout from this&amp;hellip; you want to plant it&#xA;Item Lore: It is incredibly thought-provoking, and is capable of releasing one&amp;rsquo;s mind from all cultural, social and political restraints. Many ancient books of empires and royal monarchies express a violent fear of these seeds, as they are almost bound to cause coups or revolutions when sown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/vessel-mask/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/vessel-mask/</guid>
      <description>#Void A mask, carved from bones of a intensively powerful being. It gives off a deeply unsettling, even eldritch feel. It is a ivory to bleached white plate, with any number of two to eight holes for eyes. Oftentimes, masks have been engraved or otherwise decorated. Despite their origin, they are quite fragile and prone to shattering.&#xA;In case a hollow or bearer puts it on, they&amp;rsquo;ll find themselves unable to remove it and rapidly decay into a vessel, loosing any free thought and speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/voidtouched-boots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/artifacts/voidtouched-boots/</guid>
      <description>#Item These Boots have been crafted by the Ancients in attempts to stride upon The Void. They appear as shimmering black leather boots that has been charred and turned pitch black at some parts. The sole seems to be a unidentified durable rubber or similar flexible material. The cap of each boot is reinforced with a rounded metal cap, although it&amp;rsquo;s not clear if this is steel or something else. This metal seems to pounce at bright light, and intensify shadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/bottled-embers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/bottled-embers/</guid>
      <description>#Item&#xA;This bottle is carved out of beryllium bronze with a cork/plug cut from fiery ruby. Its metal body is engraved with detailed runes and other arcane writing, which are warm to the touch.&#xA;Vessels like these are rather common containers for all kinds of magical or otherwise volatile substances, with the engravings and gem plug depending on the content.&#xA;Either acquired by magical item shop, loot, or from within Sepulchre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/bottled-smoulders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/bottled-smoulders/</guid>
      <description>#Item This bottle is carved out of beryllium bronze with a cork/plug cut from fiery ruby. Its metal body is engraved with detailed runes and other arcane writing, which are warm to the touch.&#xA;Vessels like these are rather common containers for all kinds of magical or otherwise volatile substances, with the engravings and gem plug depending on the content.&#xA;Consumable, Healing, restores 20% Stamina and Mana/Amarisk for Hollow and Undead entities Incompletely heals and reverses hollowing state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/bundle-of-medicinal-herbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/bundle-of-medicinal-herbs/</guid>
      <description>#Item&#xA;Cures one debuff/negative status effect over the course of &amp;hellip; ca 5 min irl time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/bar-of-ithildine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/bar-of-ithildine/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Commodity #Component Spirit-infused alloy which only is visible during any first quarter to last quarter of the moons or under intense light, which we have not been able to achieve outside of complex focusing optics and the circumstances in a forgery.&#xA;Highly valued and hunted-for amongst assassins and other shady folk that is active at night-time. Typically drawn or wrought into fine wire and foil to inscribe secret information aside from it&amp;rsquo;s excellent use in armour plating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/bottle-of-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/bottle-of-dreams/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Commodity #Component &amp;ldquo;Besides my bed i keep a bottle of dreams&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Created by placing a Strange Flask opened in proximity to a resting place. It has to be sealed before sunrise, or otherwise the collected dreams will leave again.&#xA;Magic component&#xA;Somewhat a amarisk condensate as dreams are unfiltered thoughts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/chunk-of-gliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/chunk-of-gliss/</guid>
      <description>#Item #commodity A decently sized chunk of Gliss, the unnatural substance surrounding the Fountainhead. It is almost entirely devoid of physical traits, which makes samples a white, smooth object with no friction or resistances whatsoever.&#xA;Heavy and unusable in its current state, but someone find this highly valuable.&#xA;This cannot be worked with regular tools. (Only magic or Laser/water cutting or magic) %% Can be sold to scientists and artisans, as they value its mass in combination to the absolute lack of friction to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/inanistathine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/inanistathine/</guid>
      <description>From Latin “Inanis” = nothing (adj.) A metal, pitch black, deeper and darker than the night and the deepest depths of the sea. It seems to be convulsing, yes, shaking. Bringing light to it seems feeble, as no torch, no candle known to us can combat the darkness it radiates. Shadows seem to grow longer and act strangely in proximity to a bar of this. What as this? Is this what pure darkness looks like, instilled upon metal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/splinter-of-blazes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/splinter-of-blazes/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Commodity #Component A searing hot splinter, seemingly struck off from a large red gem. There is a smaller coating of ash sintered onto it.&#xA;Despite being extremely hot, you can hold it like any other item.&#xA;Someone interested in high temperature applications might find this valuable.&#xA;%%Can be sold to the CoTF, possibly to upgrade bottled embers/smoulders%%</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/strange-flask/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/components-ingredients/strange-flask/</guid>
      <description>This bottle is carved out of beryllium bronze with a cork/plug cut from fiery ruby. Its metal body is engraved with detailed runes and other arcane writing, which are warm to the touch.&#xA;Vessels like these are rather common containers for all kinds of magical or otherwise volatile substances, with the engravings and gem plug depending on the content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/armour/sentinel-power-armour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/armour/sentinel-power-armour/</guid>
      <description>#equipment #Thylyist&#xA;A finely crafted armour, fuelled by clockwork and steam. With a steady supply of energy it becomes a truly intimidating piece of machinery on the battlefield.&#xA;Sentinel power amour, stolen from the Central Thylyist Armoury. One of the most powerful and strongest marvels of contemporary technology. Highly modular and customisable, plead for a hearing with War Constructor Borange Olbaz for upgrades and modification.&#xA;Possession of this asset is condemned, as the Sentinels, and by that extend, the entire Thylyian Military consider this technology top secret and will send the Hounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/climbing-glove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/climbing-glove/</guid>
      <description>Item Size: Medium Item Weight: Light Value: 1 Renu +1 for unarmed strikes&#xA;-1 dexterity&#xA;Removes penalty for climbing&#xA;These rugged, made-to-use gloves are adorned with steel claws and knuckles.&#xA;They are somewhat clumsy, but you could easily hurt someone with the pointy bits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/sea-serpent-splinter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/equipment/sea-serpent-splinter/</guid>
      <description>#equipment #elemental&#xA;Armor: Splint This fragment of the Avonian sea serpent may be mounted on or in a armour piece that spans the torso.&#xA;Magic amour If the mounted armour piece is related to magic, it&amp;rsquo;ll become able to shape water in a limited degree, such as forming bubbles underwater or concentrating atmospheric moisture into shock dampening shields.&#xA;Technical or conventional amour Technological or conventional amour will gain water repelling properties, as to avoid dysfunction or defects when inserted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/flare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/flare/</guid>
      <description>A small, cylindrical device with a protruding fuse. It is coloured bright red, with a few unknown letters written on it. If used, it will produce a extremely bright light for ten minutes, which is immune to water or magic. This light might attract unwanted attention. Prolonged exposure can easily blind someone staring at the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/potions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/potions/</guid>
      <description>Any &amp;ldquo;Time of application&amp;rdquo; is skipped if the container is thrown.&#xA;Utility Oil of Ironwork (Potion): This thin oil can cover a 5 foot cube (or equivalent volume) of iron, and takes 10 minutes to apply. At the end of that time, the volume of raw materials is converted into a cauldron inscribed with alien symbols. The quality of the object is commensurate with the quality of the raw materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/spellcasting-glove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/spellcasting-glove/</guid>
      <description>This glove, made from leather, is capable of articulating the Amarisk and Twilit flowing through the Caster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/catalogue-of-armaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/catalogue-of-armaments/</guid>
      <description>APAS Ltd. holds rights over many weapons systems, and this catalogue tries to summarise them. Among their most profitable products are Mechas and Battlesuits, who are indirectly influenced by Lavish&amp;rsquo; Bioengineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/childish-book-of-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/childish-book-of-prayers/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt One We are the Children. The Children of The Flame. The Flame&amp;hellip; Must live on. How do we know? The heat tells us. The Heart&amp;hellip; A being, a deity beyond, has sacrificed its core, for us, so that we spread the word, the heat. burn. BURN. BURN THEM ALL. &amp;gt;First Spark, First Book of Cinders, First Blaze&#xA;Preamble: That is our desire, our goal. Everyone, everything, consumed by the flame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/epos-manuscripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/epos-manuscripts/</guid>
      <description>An impressive libram written in golden ink upon aged papyrus, bound in thick leather and decorated with silver dragon scales. A list of dates, both past and future, has been added in the middle of the tome. The other pages are seemingly blank, which warrants further inspection. On the bottom edge of each page is a line, divided into segments, which leads to the assumption of a coherent timeline. It appears that this manuscript perpetually extends itself into a age-defying chronicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/ganes-parchments-of-shadows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/ganes-parchments-of-shadows/</guid>
      <description>A heavy libram bound in stained glass plates. It is sealed by fate, and can be opened only within the Court of Storms. The glass plates show signs of attempts to forcibly open it, which are visibly malformed, as if the glass melted and cooled. Attempting to raise the covers causes little arcs of electricity to jump between the reinforced edges&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s contents are fabled to be arcane secrets of the arts of necromancy and voidweaving, banished and condemned into this hulk of a tome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/nekonomicon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/nekonomicon/</guid>
      <description>book of cats or something. mew. got that feline energy and vibes, &amp;ldquo;eats&amp;rdquo; catnip^[secretly turns it into more paper] and is just overall goofy WILL knock over any other books in it&amp;rsquo;s presence, the competition is threatening!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/on-the-warfare-using-the-arcane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/on-the-warfare-using-the-arcane/</guid>
      <description>Weaponized Wizardry A collection of papers for massacre and violation using the arcane.&#xA;This tome is written in luminous ink engraved into blackened glass plates, bound in black dragon scales. It is locked by a intangible mechanism, which seems to loosen partially depending on location. %%It only opens within the Archive of Old.%%&#xA;Once unlocked, one may spend up to 8 hours per day studying it, which will each grant knowledge about taking magic onto the battlefield, such as a recipe, spell, or ritual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/the-celestial-compendium-of-schi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/the-celestial-compendium-of-schi/</guid>
      <description>An impressive tome bound in once-polished, now-rusted iron plates set with a large but fractured emerald. It is said to be written by the wizards and sages of the Athenaeum of Sorcery. It&amp;rsquo;s sheer weight and appearance raised many rumours in arcane societies, and it is said to hold secrets about sailing the Eternal Sea.&#xA;It can be opened without issue, however, it is written in a scripture that you can&amp;rsquo;t read, it feels like it is actively trying to escape your mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/the-elvos-incunabulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/the-elvos-incunabulum/</guid>
      <description>A compendium bound in thin marble slates set with round moonstone. It is locked with a intricate mechanism which seems to resemble the local constellations. Closer observation has resulted that the various planets on the cover move, according to their real position. This leads to the conclusion that it only might open during a special constellation or arrangement.&#xA;Perhaps someone versed with the night sky might be able to help?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/tomes-of-twilit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/tomes-of-twilit/</guid>
      <description>The Ways of using Amarisk A large, locked coffer made from hardened steel, adorned with silver dragon scales. It is filled to the brim with plain, leather-bound scriptures. Each of these smaller books appears to be covered in a slight ethereal haze, which grows thicker if the books are moved haphazardly or read too quickly.&#xA;Contents Requirements For a individual to be able to conduct and weave Twilit into elementary forces, one must:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/tomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/tomes/</guid>
      <description>A heavy libram bound in stained glass plates. It is sealed by fate, and can be opened only within the Court of Storms. The glass plates show signs of attempts to forcibly open it, which are visibly malformed, as if the glass melted and cooled. Attempting to raise the covers causes little arcs of electricity to jump between the reinforced edges&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s contents are fabled to be arcane secrets of the arts of necromancy and voidweaving, banished and condemned into this hulk of a tome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/dead-childs-lullaby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/dead-childs-lullaby/</guid>
      <description>Oh little one, don&amp;rsquo;t you worry, It&amp;rsquo;ll be alright. Charon will come and bring you home. No, don&amp;rsquo;t shed tears, for your family is here. Don&amp;rsquo;t you worry, poor one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/his-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/his-design/</guid>
      <description>Through conception and planning; ideas refined, polished till perfection. In His Image we plan, construct, assemble. Our Blessed Machine guides the way through Providence to Ascension. The flesh will spoil, rot, nothing but bones remain of the former self. Yet, the newborn self remains driven by oxygen and blood, a heirloom and legacy of its origins. A stark warning to those&amp;hellip; The foul energies haunting our realm prevent one&amp;rsquo;s spirit to depart, to migrate away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/providence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/texts-books-written-things/true-machinists-scriptures/providence/</guid>
      <description>From the moment I understood the weakness of my flesh, it disgusted me. I craved the strength and certainty of steel. I aspired to the purity of the Blessed Machine. Your kind cling to your flesh, as though it will not decay and fail you. One day the crude biomass you call the temple will wither, and you will beg my kind to save you. But I am already saved, for The Machine is immortal… Even in death I serve Mekhane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/travel/rat-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/travel/rat-cart/</guid>
      <description>This sturdy wooden cart is supported by four over-sized treadwheels, each of which contains a magical rat. The cart can carry up to 2000 pounds of weight, and balances itself. It moves at a speed of 40 ft. for up to eight hours per day, but never between midnight to dawn. The cart follows your simple verbal commands to start, stop, turn, etc. Each rat may be fed1 daily for a hour of extra performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/travel/riftstones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/travel/riftstones/</guid>
      <description>#Travel A small stone, worked to resemble a regular geometric shape. A glowing, fluctuating coloured line runs over the entire stone, dividing it in two halves. One face has the divider widen into what resembles a keyhole, which also takes on another geometric shape. You obtained a key with it, which fits perfectly into the breach.&#xA;It seems to magnetically attract the key&amp;hellip;&#xA;When the Key is inserted, the divider will vanish, dropping the two shells and open up a temporary rift to any bound location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/childs-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/childs-staff/</guid>
      <description>#Weapon #elemental #Children-of-the-Flame&#xA;Staff&#xA;Origin: Elemental Fire. The item was forged through the power of elemental fire by Crimson Heart. It is hot to the touch, likely red or orange, and is made from boron steel. It has heat or fire-based powers, and can cause local violations of thermodynamics to source heat.&#xA;Major Property: Elemental Cursing. This Staff strikes its victims with intense, localised bursts of elemental heat, which will burn, scar and cauterise the targeted area, causing horrible wounds that will not heal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/cyphers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/cyphers/</guid>
      <description>%%basically one-time use spells, they loose function/self-destruct afterwards. compatible with ommoran firearms, especially the RCL0.%% Greater cyphers simply loose their power after activation, lesser cyphers shatter or disintegrate. Superior cyphers may be used several times, but will discharge in a chain when force is acted upon it. Greater cyphers may be &amp;ldquo;recharged&amp;rdquo; by re-applying their lost power/catalyst using a spell/ritual. Also applies for superior cyphers, as long as they remain intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/electric-ukulele/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/electric-ukulele/</guid>
      <description>#Weapon And his music was electric. Finest and most exotic wood, strung with exotic metal, but bearing smoulders, through which lightning bore its way.&#xA;Stats Finest and most exotic wood, strung with exotic metal, but bearing smoulders, through which lightning bore its way.&#xA;Stats Bard&amp;rsquo;s weapon. Any enemy in ranged attack radius will suffer 4d4+2 electric damage per round and 1d6 minutes of paralysation. Metal armour may provide immunity against these attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/mace-of-the-black-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/mace-of-the-black-one/</guid>
      <description>#Weapon #Item Weapon (mace)&#xA;Origin: Void. This Item was forged by no other than Warlock Gaíz-an, for itself to send out into the world and curse whatever poor soul finds it. It is an asymmetrical item made of black iron, smeared paste, and it bears screaming faces and dark runes. Its powers may cause madness, undeath, deformation or maiming, disease, pain, decay, or something else horrible. It may also be capable of dirigating Night Runners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/onis-glaive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/melee/onis-glaive/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Weapon Origin: Oni. This item was created by an oni. It is dark, blue-tinted, and surrounded by a visible magic aura. It is large, but may scale to a size appropriate for its wielder. Its powers are designed to be used by the oni to stalk its victims, and might involve shapechanging, mind control, invisibility, darkness, or stealth.&#xA;Major Property: Bulwark. The user of this item has advantage on saving throws made to maintain concentration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/propelled-projectile/oa-ws-bst-model-7%E2%81%BF/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/propelled-projectile/oa-ws-bst-model-7%E2%81%BF/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Weapon %%Ballistic Spell Test, model/iteration 7%%&#xA;Origin: Lost. The creators of this weapon succumbed to the tooth of time and vanished from the face of earth. Only their exquisite craftsmanship in Arcane Engineering and weaponry remains. Restorative work has revealed the company as &amp;ldquo;Ommoran Arms Weapons Systems&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;A break-open hand pistol, modified to be capable of using spell scrolls, runes and similar arcane carriers as ammunition. A slight modification to a usual handgun is that the chamber is made from a indiscernible blackened metal and the pin seems to be some orange glowing gem or mineral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/propelled-projectile/oa-ws-rcl-mk.40%E1%B5%90%E1%B5%90/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/weaponry/propelled-projectile/oa-ws-rcl-mk.40%E1%B5%90%E1%B5%90/</guid>
      <description>#Item #Weapon Origin: Lost. %%Varuú grenade launcher for stronger cyphers. Ranged Cypher Launcher %% This peculiar piece of handheld weaponry features seven tubes on a rotary drum, each of which appear to be fitted silver, engraved with runes. Contrary to that, the entire frame except the grips (back and main trigger) appear as dull, greyish-black metal, which is cold to the touch. The drum can be swayed to the side at the touch of a rune above its axle, presumably for loading the tubes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/bag-of-crickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/bag-of-crickets/</guid>
      <description>A Bag of Holding, specifically tailored to hold a near-infinite amount of crickets to release unto a foe. Comes with 100,000 crickets from the get-go! Someone with a taste for smaller insects might accept them instead of currency.&#xA;Disrupt the local ecosystem for the low price of 22.99€!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/iron-oculus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/iron-oculus/</guid>
      <description>Wondrous #Item This hollow iron sphere is inscribed with an eye-like iris, and a brass hinge and clasp allow it to open.&#xA;You can use an action to hold the open oculus to your eye and speak its command word. Upon activation, one of your eyes is drawn into the sphere, leaving an empty socket and dealing 1d4 armour-piercing damage. While your eye is trapped and you are holding the oculus, you have darkvision out to a range of 5 meters, and can detect polymorphed and shapechanged creatures and objects within 5 meters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/polished-silver-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/polished-silver-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Starting item for those with a familiar.&#xA;A fancily polished silver mirror. The grip is plentifully engraved with Runes.&#xA;If capable of reading Chinetic: &amp;ldquo;Spirits, Travel, Journey, Me | I, possess, power&amp;rdquo;&#xA;To summon the attuned familiar spirit (2 actions to summon, one to give instructions)&#xA;chant, calling the spirit by name: Hearken to these words Hear my cry I call to you spirit from the other side I wish to speak to you here Come to me Come to this mirror I call you now, (spirits name)!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/soulstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/soulstone/</guid>
      <description>A glass-clear rock, partially encrusted with regular stone. A few impurities and cracks stain the sight, which seem to shift by themselves. It is capable of absorbing the final echo of someone’s consciousness in the case of a ultimate demise. It can also be used to chain a spirit to the material plane for easy recall, or be a beacon and navigation aid to a voluntarily contracted spirit.&#xA;Starting item to those with a bound familiar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/stop-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/items/wondrous-and-wack/stop-box/</guid>
      <description>==Wondrous Item== This small box, coloured black and yellow, features a prominent red knob on top of it, along with the engraved word &amp;ldquo;STOP&amp;rdquo;. When the button is pressed, the environment around the activating person is seemingly frozen in time until the button is released, or a subjective minute has passed. Time from the perspective of others passes regularly, the activator is just capable of doing a few extremely rapid moves.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
