<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faction on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/faction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faction on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/faction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</guid>
      <description>Overview The specialised brigade of the Gearforged Vanguard, unshackled from the regressive preachings of the Mekhanites. Tasked to channel His Design into machines that kill, maim and burn, this ward holds the responsibility of many-a such creations, reckless and carefree of the impact of their monstrosities. ^87a079&#xA;People involved Despite being among the highest secrets of Thylyist, one or two names slipped into the general public. It is known that War Constructor Borange Olbaz is among their highest ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/differences-regarding-factions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/differences-regarding-factions/</guid>
      <description>Thylyist Boons Attunement to all things mechanical Easy access to various military and economic resources Possibly acquiring Thylyian Military supplies legally or through conscription/service Drawbacks Narrative adjustments There‘s no world outside of Thylyist No Tech greater than gear, steam and steel Magic? doesn‘t exist&#xA;Kill-on-Sight orders from Dragonkin, Frisco and Exile/Nolka&#xA;Sepulchre Boons Sense of community; shared goods across the necropolis (i.e. less requirements for money) Diplomatic relations to Frisco Indirect access to both Thylyian and Friscoan Tech, Items and weaponry Access to the trains Drawbacks Treat/Property „Undying“ mandatory Prone to hollowing Outsider mentality and treatment by others Frisco Davern Exiled/Nølkā Kva’al </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/faction-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/overviews/summaries/faction-overview/</guid>
      <description>Empire of Thylyist Former city-state, grown to the size of a empire. The City of Thylyist is their capital, and epicentre of their official religion, the Followers of Mekhane, originally conceived as bunker-fort installation shortly before the end of the Nølkā-Mekhanite War. Their government is practically defunct. Instead, the religious elite (Council of Thylyist), and to a extend, the Gearforged Vanguard is de-facto ruling. The fanatical devotion impacts everyday life and has frozen technological and scientific progress, leaving them stuck in early steam-driven technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/areas/empire-of-thylyist/empire-of-thylyist/</guid>
      <description>Capital of the human population; highly advanced in mechanics and metalworking. However, they are strictly conservative, if not regressive, about more advanced technology due to their religious dogmata. The Archive within the lowest Levels feature the staggering history of Thylyist: they eradicated The Lavish Empire after abusing them to forcibly relocate the god-gone Nølkā. -&amp;gt; The Second Era Amida&amp;rsquo;s sector structure is derived from the fact that Thylyist already existed as megacity with several layers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/sepulchre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/ninth-forest/sepulchre/</guid>
      <description>The undying City #Undead #Settlements #Faction&#xA;The main settlement 1 for victims of the Curse of the Undead.&#xA;Only a smaller fraction of the residents voluntarily lives here, most of them got forcibly sent here, oftentimes through concentration camp-like treatment from certain governmental bodies.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s underground, and they have a small religion going on, but it drifted too far into states that a alive and integer mind cannot parse. +1d4 insanity on inspect The main place of worship of their religion is said to be built atop a Lichen relic vault, which has been cemented there before the Great Woe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/city-of-stargard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/realms/utuw-system/schi/servilia/regions/sea-major/astral-ocean/ka%C3%A1-rav-isles/city-of-stargard/</guid>
      <description>Overview A community of isolated and deranged sorcerers who devote their time towards the study and use of celestial bodies and formations. A decent part of their population is made from other outcasts and strangers.&#xA;The only remaining actively practising guild for Astral Sorcery. Townsfolk and activity are only seen past sundown and cease after sunrise; during the day, every citizen sleeps until nightfall. There are only few accommodations and housing-for-hire that offer a &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; opening schedule for foreigners.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
