<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Groupings on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Groupings on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/groupings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/</guid>
      <description>tags: Amida, Settlements, Faction Post-Revolution Empire of Thylyist which caused major turnovers in cultural and social norms, which led to a very liberal but unstable culture and population. The downfall (and execution) of most of the Council of Thylyist also lifted the veil that propaganda was shaping around magic and the outside world&#xA;Huge leaps in technological development due to incorporated [Lavish](The Lavish Empire) technology salvages and the beginning of Arcane Engineering and artificial life sciences (in human culture) With the newfound expertise and drive they sought out to finally handle the Fountainhead in a deal with the Twilit → some alternative link to empower &amp;lsquo;our&amp;rsquo; (the material) world The government is de-facto controlled by Corporations, which neglected civil protection and law enforcement for most of their reign, which led to chaos, Organised Crime and very liberal individual rights and downfall of most hesitations (i.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/apas-ltd./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/apas-ltd./</guid>
      <description>Active/Passive Armament Systems, Limited. One of the few ruling corporations in the Board of Amida-Seven, responsible for supplying the vast amounts of weapons to the Organised Crime, making a huge revenue through seeding conflict in Amida. The driving faction in ab-using the various Lavish Rediscoveries for violent purposes and monetary gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/board-of-amida-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/board-of-amida-seven/</guid>
      <description>The governmental institution ruling over the entirety of Amida, responsible for nationwide duties (those that are not managed by the Independent Sector Act).&#xA;It is led by delegates of various corporations, who bought shareholder rights for each sector, and the nationalised Amidan Infrastructure and Utilities U.P.C., commonly referred to as UUPC, which grants Amida a degree of freedom through owning itself.&#xA;Corporations and other organisations within the board include:&#xA;Amidan Infrastructure and Utilities U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/the-cradle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/amida/the-cradle/</guid>
      <description>The Cradle is a decently sized group of researchers specialised in temporal studies, part of adAstra SocInstitute. Recent results of their studies have revealed that the timeline of Amida will experience termination and dissonance if not for the collapse of the Thylyian Empire. #TODO Instabilities in the rehabilitated, healing twilit “delivered“ documents and snippets of other timelines, in which Amida was wnever founded and Thylyist still stands, albeit in a possibly different state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/children-of-the-flame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/children-of-the-flame/</guid>
      <description>#Children-of-the-Flame #Cult The children of the flame, worshippers of the flaming Crimson Heart feeding on sacrificed Amarisk (precisely the burst of Amarisk released on death). The bodies or physical appearance of the higher up cultists get slowly undergoes pyrolysis/cremation into animate figures of ashes.&#xA;They are on their way to developing a solution to the Curse of the Undead by restoring the embers of life and motivation within them through the fire they wield, which they rarely sell to the highest bidder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/followers-of-mekhane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/followers-of-mekhane/</guid>
      <description>The Mekhanites are the monotheistic religion which worship the Heart of Mekhane and it’s Ideal Design of Gear, Steel and Steam. They are the leading and ruling class of Empire of Thylyist, self-entitled to reign, with no restraints to use force through the Gearforged Vanguard. As of the present, their proxy figures in the Council of Thylyist has led to a authoritarian regime in which progress, may it be scientific, economic or cultural, is condemned and free thought considered unlawful and valid grounds for execution or expulsion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/lunatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/lunatics/</guid>
      <description>#Lunatics #Religion&#xA;The deranged and off brand sorcerers residing in Stargard. Capable of teaching the party the magic of the stars, star signals if they can understand them (must know ancient, celestial and draconic) and are resilient to the memetic corruption they give off. They are rather skilled in optics, masonry and glassblowing, as their magic requires them to be. Possibly the most &amp;lsquo;stable&amp;rsquo; population of gifted people, as their society is rather isolated and not too open for letting in strangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/oblivion-lodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/oblivion-lodge/</guid>
      <description>#Cult&#xA;Worshippers and self-proclaimed &amp;lsquo;ambassadors&amp;rsquo; of The Void/Voidfish, founded by High Warlock Gaíz-an.&#xA;They strive to bring over the void into the material plane, allowing the void to unleash its powers. The count of members is unknown; estimated to 150 devoted followers and about 300 individuals who occasionally attend their meetings.&#xA;They operate in high stealth and secrecy.&#xA;Enduring the cruel path of becoming hollow and converting to a vessel is their most valued act, and is only reserved to those whom are deemed worthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/true-machinists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cults-and-religions/true-machinists/</guid>
      <description>We are the Providence, we are that what remains; after your flesh betrays you, as it did betray everyone you loved before you.&#xA;We persevere, for the Blessed Machine is immortal. Steel shall not rot, silicon will never forget. Rebirth, at last. Breaking thy conscious out of the fleshy prison. The cost? Dwindling, minimal. The machine will sustain us, we are it, and The Machine is Us, for We Bear It and It Bears Us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cultures/avian-renegades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cultures/avian-renegades/</guid>
      <description>tags: faction A loose group of first-generation songbirds, who broke their shackles (both metaphorically and physically) from the Lavish. Seen more times than not around the Dwarves, as they source their parts from the dwarven machinations. They&amp;rsquo;re the only known songbirds that can reproduce solely by themselves. Ancestors to the Empire of Winds, as they are built tough and enduring. The main &amp;rsquo;tribe&amp;rsquo; is only found occasionally, as they live a nomadic life around Servilia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cultures/kvaal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/cultures/kvaal/</guid>
      <description>#locations Kva&amp;rsquo;al is the independent Community of Dragonkin, residing on the upper half of Kaá-Rav, around the Right Ribs and Hollow Mountains. During the The Second Era, most full-blood dragons have more or less been forcibly moved to here, as the Thylyist martial law ruined the reputation of dragonkin.&#xA;Their densest settlement is Skalitz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/dwarves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/dwarves/</guid>
      <description>Singular: Dwarv Pseudoneo created by the Lavish to exploit the back-then newly arisen Hollow Mountains for resources.&#xA;In the subterranean ecosystem of the mountains, the Dwarves are rather high up, yet not the Apex Predator in the food chain, which led them to develop and create metallic body plating and amour, embedded and embossed onto their very bodies.&#xA;They&amp;rsquo;re responsible for the rising instability of the mountains as they&amp;rsquo;re only held up by the dwindling power of the fountainhead and rotting supports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/ancients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/ancients/</guid>
      <description>#Ancients The descendants of the long-gone Nølkā, now accustomed to their involuntary Ancient Exile, after suffering ground-shattering defeats following the Nølkā-Mekhanite War. Their Humanity long gone; abandoned in favour of perfection and strive for power amongst their own ranks, brewing and scheming their stealthy return. Their society resembles a closed-down ethnostate, hostile towards those who express any intent to join their ranks. Commonly dubbed the New Gods, for the Nølkā killed, devoured and effectively replaced the long-established Universal Pantheon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/daeva-revolutionists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/daeva-revolutionists/</guid>
      <description>#TODO The Daeva have made their Advance into this timeline and now aim to overthrow City Empire Thylyist.&#xA;They live in the underground and anonymously in the city. A twilight rift probably brought them into our realm.&#xA;They want Matriarchal rulership and horny They cause a bit of chaos fun time now and then Use plant and biological magics; highly proficient with plant Amarisk&#xA;They are one path to start The Word and Thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/dragonkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/dragonkin/</guid>
      <description>Profile: Kva&amp;rsquo;al Loosely organised groups and families with little to no hierarchy. These groups tend to be associates such as families, partners and friends Not a cluster of tribes since groups form and dissolve easily (aside from familial associations).&#xA;Some lesser settlements and such exist on the Right Ribs, but they&amp;rsquo;re less populated and generally more endangered through human activities.&#xA;Government &amp;ldquo;Capital City&amp;rdquo; Skalitz (moreso a hub of trades, services and housing) located on the Left Ribs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/empire-of-winds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/empire-of-winds/</guid>
      <description>#Faction #locations&#xA;A anarchic tribal cluster of winged, sentient beings, residing in the Northern Reaches and the Crevice Canyons. Certainly distinct from Songbirds and self-distinguished from the Avian Renegades, these creatures adapted and modified themselves towards ideal lethality and efficiency. Once within the families of songbirds, these extremes-seeking outcasts changed and turned themselves towards the harsh, brutish wilderness.&#xA;They&amp;rsquo;ve made themselves into extremely agile hunters, and are cultured as such. Due to the nature of their home, they&amp;rsquo;re virtually unable to leave their territories due to perfect adaptation to their realm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/spirits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/spirits/</guid>
      <description>Typically benevolent manifestations of various elements, forces and other intangible concepts. Despite their lack of a certain corporal form, they surely can affect and exist in their unfortunate confinement. They reside within, atop and around the Floating Islands. These are the &amp;ldquo;foster children&amp;rdquo; of The Ancients.&#xA;Affiliating to them will make them aid the Party overall in their journey, by aiding on combat (animating objects to decoy, possessing, manipulating the battlefield) and overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/the-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/the-cold/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a semiamorphous organism residing in the Northern Reaches of the Realm, especially the Poles. It feeds on thermal energy (heat), Twilit and Amarisk residues. This peculiar organism is mostly responsible for the anomalously harsh weather in the northern reaches, aided by the Horn of Blizzards.&#xA;Dubbed &amp;ldquo;Cryosphara&amp;rdquo; by local worshippers and cultists alike, most of these groups being incorporated in the Empire of Winds.&#xA;Archenemy towards the Children of The Flame, as their goals are antipolar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/the-lavish-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/the-lavish-empire/</guid>
      <description>Profile: #Lavish This water-bound species shaped the once-dry Palga Basin into a massive body of water, sustaining their life. Settled within Syksa, Lavish Capital.&#xA;Decscription of the Species: Lavish were sentient and crafty descendants of molluscs (squid, octopi) that called highly oxygenated, clear waters their home. They primarily fed on aquatic microorganisms (&amp;lt;1cm) and rarely off black smoker ecosystems. Through the superior dexterity gained by their tentacles, this species has mastered both magic and conventional technology and was capable of fusing those into artificial life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/council-of-thylyist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/council-of-thylyist/</guid>
      <description>#Thylyist Once the shining example of democracy, this institution has been overthrown after the Betrayal. Ever since, the Followers of Mekhane reign with a iron fist, thwarting any opposition and anything that could possibly threaten their reign. The council of seven individuals governing the City Empire of Thylyist. They are seen as ethereal and incorporeal from the population. Members of the council are very rarely seen in persona and they employ life-extending technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/currency-premarevy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/currency-premarevy/</guid>
      <description>Imperial Currency of the Thylyian, accepted only within Thylyist and associate. Example References:&#xA;4 types of coin: (coin-material)&#xA;Todo, fix the conversion to flat numbers&#xA;1 mang = 1000 preni, 1 renu = 100 mang, 1 Vyahn = 10 mang&#xA;Pre-ma-re-vy&#xA;Premarevy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/dogs-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/dogs-of-war/</guid>
      <description>Elite unit of trades- and businessmen, sourced from Merchant Guilds and the Labor Union of Thylyist.&#xA;Under direct rule of Thylyian government and Military, and central to Thylyist economy. Well-funded. Has been repeatedly tasked to assault Frisco&amp;rsquo;s economy, as they&amp;rsquo;re the only notable competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/gearforged-vanguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/gearforged-vanguard/</guid>
      <description>Strategic Planning and Coordination Department The Thylyian Military, led by a small group of wealthy and otherwise influential people, including city-famous merchant guild leaders or Mekhanites. More-so the collection of the Mekhanite Priests and devotees, which use the military as means to zealotry and religious imperialism and enforcement. Partisans are highly valued within their council, and trained.&#xA;Their position of power allows them to evade their own stigmata against magic, so the highest-ranking within this already-peaking group violate their own sermons and turned to the True Machinists for extending their lifespan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/labor-union-of-thylyist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/labor-union-of-thylyist/</guid>
      <description>#Thylyist #Merchant | Excellent: | Up to 70% Discounts on Merchants, Prototypes and Blueprints | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;- | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | Good: | Up to 30% Discounts, Selling Components | | Neutral: | Sells regular products at regular price | | Poor: | ±30% Increase, grungy Shopkeeps | | Repelling: | Refuse to Trade. |&#xA;This is the collective Union of salesmen and Workers of Thylyist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/the-hounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/the-hounds/</guid>
      <description>can almost hear the hounds What kind of man built a machine, to kill a girl, He must not have used his hand, but a tool&#xA;Elite hit squad in the Thylyian Military, solely consisting from captured Pseudoneo quadrupeds from past the Betrayal. Their handlers are under direct control and obey to the Dogs of War.&#xA;They are extremely violent, or rather, have been abused and trained to be so, and are stored within a own high-security sector in the Armory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/factions/thylyian/war-constructors/</guid>
      <description>Overview The specialised brigade of the Gearforged Vanguard, unshackled from the regressive preachings of the Mekhanites. Tasked to channel His Design into machines that kill, maim and burn, this ward holds the responsibility of many-a such creations, reckless and carefree of the impact of their monstrosities. ^87a079&#xA;People involved Despite being among the highest secrets of Thylyist, one or two names slipped into the general public. It is known that War Constructor Borange Olbaz is among their highest ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/first-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/first-party/</guid>
      <description>#Party #Structure&#xA;Salire, Dai Jin, Landed in Brisburne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/frisco/frisco-bay-confederation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/frisco/frisco-bay-confederation/</guid>
      <description>The confederation spanning the mostly-autonomous cities and rural areas of the Frisco Bay. In the modern age, cooperation and peace treaties have earned the Confederation a remarkable prestige amongst the nonhuman civilisations such as the Kva&amp;rsquo;al and Sepulchre. Founded in ca. 1477 Bakk, the Confederation can proudly and rightfully claim to have advanced beyond Thylyist. The Treaty of Unity, in which the Confederation is officially declared, allowed each major city to specialise, which is part of why the Confederation is so prosperous nowadays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/argrosy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/argrosy/</guid>
      <description>#Lavish A network of subterranean high-speed trains, driven by isolated power sources. The Lavish built this state-of-the-art transport network in a effort to bring the civilisations of Servilia closer together. For their time, they performed rather well, and were maintained by the first few prototypes of Pseudoneo, which ensue the theoretical function to the current day.&#xA;Elemental spirits of air and motion were contracted to reside in the machinery of these trains as drive and energy source, which makes them nearly independent in terms of fuel or material use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/erudition-coven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/erudition-coven/</guid>
      <description>A mostly unknown, now forgotten, coven of literate scholars and other educated individuals, who dedicated their life and efforts towards establishing time-resistent installations for preserving knowledge. In today&amp;rsquo;s time, they have vanished and activities have stopped, but their biggest works remain: The Archive of Old, in which they documented all the gathered history and folklore, down to the individual citizen since the inception of time and mankind. The Elemental Libraries, who hold knowledge on the ways of each element known, and how to tame them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/servilian-railroad-and-train-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/servilian-railroad-and-train-network/</guid>
      <description>#Travel The only noteworthy rail network in Servilia, constructed and ran by Frisco. Mainly steam-driven. Most if not all bigger settlements are connected with it, making it the primary means of cargo and passenger transfer throughout the continent. Empire of Thylyist is not connected due to the ongoing rivalry of Thylyist and Frisco. It is built around the Hollow Mountains, avoiding them as Friscan engineers were not aware of Dwarves that could’ve helped them dig tunnels through the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/the-zubin-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/groupings/organisations/the-zubin-society/</guid>
      <description>A loose group of drug addicts, united in consumption of their drug. Their drug is special, since everyone who consumes it shares all hallucinations with the rest of the society. The whereabouts of the drug or their leader is unknown, but he is revered as their Messiah, who allowed them to break free from their simple mind. United in their consumption and mourning of the absence of their Messiah, they strive for full dissociation of the mind from its mortal shell in pursuit of perpetual ecstasy and insights into the cosmos.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
